<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 18:00:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the Clouds: Achieving a Unified Security Stance and threat-based approach to Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/securing-the-clouds-achieving-a-unified-security-stance-and/ba-p/4073446</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:51:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/securing-the-clouds-achieving-a-unified-security-stance-and/ba-p/4073446</guid>
      <description>Note: this is the second of a four-part blog series that explores the complexities of securing multiple clouds and the limitations of traditional Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) tools.
&#160;
With the first post, we discussed the importance of adopting a multi-cloud approach to Observability, centralizing in a single SIEM all the events generated by your infrastructure to enable a more comprehensive analysis of potential security incidents by correlating events independently from their origin. We also hinted to the complexity of such endeavor.You can read the first post here:&#160;Secur...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Permissions Management: Defender XDR's RBAC Walkthrough for Microsoft Defender for Office 365</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-office/permissions-management-defender-xdr-s-rbac-walkthrough-for/ba-p/4064288</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:50:12 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-office/permissions-management-defender-xdr-s-rbac-walkthrough-for/ba-p/4064288</guid>
      <description>We are very excited about the Microsoft Defender XDR RBAC announcement as GA on December 2023, also available in GCC, GCC-High, and DoD environments.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Microsoft Defender XDR unified role-based access control is the new permissions model across the various Defender workloads, and&#160;is a critical step forward in our &#8220;least privilege&#8221; permissions principle for Microsoft Defender for Office 365.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Instead of managing permissions to access Defender for Office in 3 different portals (Microsoft Entra ID, the Defender portal and Exchange Admin Center), Defender XDR RBAC allows Security Operation Ce...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use Sensitive Info Types to classify your structured data assets at column level</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/use-sensitive-info-types-to-classify-your-structured-data-assets/ba-p/4038292</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:44:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/use-sensitive-info-types-to-classify-your-structured-data-assets/ba-p/4038292</guid>
      <description>We are excited to announce that Microsoft Purview has extended the support of Sensitive info types (SITs) to Azure and 3P data assets in the Data Map/Catalog. Before this release, SITs could only be applied at file level. Now, you can apply SITs more granularly, i.e., at column level, for structured non-M365 assets. This helps you get additional visibility in Know Your Data (KYD) scenarios.
&#160;
You can&#160;apply SITs to Azure and 3P data objects manually or automatically, including built-in and custom SITs. Sensitivity labels are derived automatically from SITs. And you can create reports related to...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
