<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:08:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to deploy Microsoft Purview DSPM for AI to secure your AI apps</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/how-to-deploy-microsoft-purview-dspm-for-ai-to-secure-your-ai/ba-p/4397714</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/how-to-deploy-microsoft-purview-dspm-for-ai-to-secure-your-ai/ba-p/4397714</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Purview Data Security Posture Management (DSPM for AI) is designed to enhance data security for the following AI applications:

Microsoft Copilot experiences, including Microsoft 365 Copilot.
Enterprise AI apps, including ChatGPT enterprise integration.
Other AI apps, including all other AI applications like ChatGPT consumer, Microsoft Copilot, DeepSeek, and Google Gemini, accessed through the browser.

In this blog, we will dive into the different policies and reporting we have to discover, protect and govern these three types of AI applications.
Prerequisites
Please refer to the pr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Use Cases of ADMS Application Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/exploring-the-use-cases-of-adms-application-pipeline/ba-p/4404097</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/exploring-the-use-cases-of-adms-application-pipeline/ba-p/4404097</guid>
      <description>A Comprehensive Overview:
An Insight into Active Directory Migration Services Application Pipeline.
Introduction
ADMS, ADSS, and ADGMS are all cloud-based services that come within the ADxS services portfolio offered by Microsoft and designed to facilitate efficient and cost-effective migrations. For additional information around migration use cases, refer to this blog:&#160;https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/blog/microsoft-security-blog/exploring-the-use-cases-of-adxs-services/4373299?previewMessage=true&#160;. In this blog, we will examine the various use cases of ADMS application pipeline, highlight...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
