<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:10:43 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender for APIs enriches Defender CSPM capabilities.</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-defender-for-apis-enriches-defender-cspm-capabilities/ba-p/3866894</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 12:06:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-defender-for-apis-enriches-defender-cspm-capabilities/ba-p/3866894</guid>
      <description>We are excited to unveil the integration of (Preview) and Defender CSPM in the Microsoft Defender for Cloud (MDC) to provide contextual API security findings and guide prioritized remediation. Microsoft Defender for APIs, announced at RSA 2023, is the latest addition to our lineup of robust Defender plans in Microsoft Defender for Cloud. Defender for APIs helps organizations' business-critical APIs managed by Azure API Management with a holistic approach to&#160;prevent, detect and respond to API security threats with integrated cloud security context.
Improve API Security Posture:Misconfigured API...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#8217;s new: Monitor and optimize the execution of your scheduled analytics rules</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/what-s-new-monitor-and-optimize-the-execution-of-your-scheduled/ba-p/3864083</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:24:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/what-s-new-monitor-and-optimize-the-execution-of-your-scheduled/ba-p/3864083</guid>
      <description>&#160;
Recently, we announced new capabilities to help Monitor the health and audit the integrity of your analytics rules. With Analytics Health Monitoring, organizations can get insights into the health, rule running details  and status of each analytics rule execution. This includes information on whether the execution succeeded or failed, along with the reason for any failures. You might be wondering what to do if you encounter a failed execution and want to re-run it within a specific window for validation after fixing it. We now offer an easy solution for this scenario.
&#160;
We are pleased to ann...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
