<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 17:01:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>New Threat Actor Intel Profiles Added to MDTI</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-threat/new-threat-actor-intel-profiles-added-to-mdti/ba-p/3841181</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 16:44:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-threat/new-threat-actor-intel-profiles-added-to-mdti/ba-p/3841181</guid>
      <description>The Microsoft Defender Threat Intelligence (Defender TI) team has recently launched twenty-six new threat actor Intel Profiles&#160;and more than 50 additional articles customers can leverage immediately to take an intel-led approach to defend their organization from the latest threats.&#160;
&#160;
Intel Profiles are a single source of information that fully licensed security operations teams can use for instant insight into the threat ecosystem. Users can rapidly identify adversary-threat infrastructure and access actionable indicators of compromise (IOCs) and in-depth analysis of tools, tactics, and proce...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using MDTI with the Diamond Model for Threat Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-threat/using-mdti-with-the-diamond-model-for-threat-intelligence/ba-p/3976100</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 16:42:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-threat/using-mdti-with-the-diamond-model-for-threat-intelligence/ba-p/3976100</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity incidents can be complex and challenging to investigate, requiring advanced tools and techniques to identify the scope of the attack, determine the adversary's tactics and procedures, and develop an effective response strategy. Microsoft Defender Threat Intelligence (MDTI) provides robust tools and features that enable security analysts to quickly investigate incidents and respond to cyber threats by applying the Diamond Model for Intrusion Analysis Framework to threat intelligence.
&#160;
The Diamond Model is a framework for understanding cyber threats that was first introduced by Se...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
