<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:00:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Question about TLS and Cipher Suite configuration</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/frequently-asked-question-about-tls-and-cipher-suite/ba-p/3965784</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/frequently-asked-question-about-tls-and-cipher-suite/ba-p/3965784</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Microsoft does not endorse the products listed in this article. They are provided for informational purposes and their listing does not constitute an endorsement. We do not guarantee the quality, safety, or effectiveness of listed products and disclaim liability for any related issues. Users should exercise their own judgment, conduct research, and seek professional advice before purchasing or using any listed products.
&#160;
Disclaimer: This article contains content generated by&#160;Microsoft Copilot.
&#160;
What versions of Windows support TLS 1.3?
Starting with Windows Server 2022, TLS 1.3 i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Permissions Management: Microsoft Defender XDR's RBAC Walkthrough for Microsoft Defender</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-office/navigating-permissions-management-microsoft-defender-xdr-s-rbac/ba-p/4064288</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-office/navigating-permissions-management-microsoft-defender-xdr-s-rbac/ba-p/4064288</guid>
      <description>We are very excited about the Microsoft Defender XDR RBAC announcement as GA on December 2023, also available in GCC, GCC-High, and DoD environments.&#160;&#160;
Microsoft Defender XDR unified role-based access control is the new permissions model across the various Defender workloads, and&#160;is a critical step forward in our &#8220;least privilege&#8221; permissions principle for Microsoft Defender for Office 365.&#160;&#160;
Instead of managing permissions to access Defender for Office in 3 different portals (Microsoft Entra ID, the Defender portal and Exchange Admin Center), Defender XDR RBAC allows Security Operation Center...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
