<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:25:19 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing File Attachments for Case Management</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/announcing-file-attachments-for-case-management/ba-p/4408881</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/announcing-file-attachments-for-case-management/ba-p/4408881</guid>
      <description>Staying informed with the most up to date information is critical to quickly taking appropriate action on a case.&#160; File Attachments for Case Management enables you to share reports, emails, screenshots, log files, and more, all in one centralized location within a case ensuring you have all the information you need.&#160;&#160;
Key Benefits of Attachments for Case Management&#160;

Centralized Information: File attachments ensure that all relevant documents, images, and data are stored in one place. No more hunting through emails or disparate systems&#8212;everything you need is right at your fingertips within the...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing File Attachments for Case Management</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/announcing-file-attachments-for-case-management/ba-p/4408877</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/announcing-file-attachments-for-case-management/ba-p/4408877</guid>
      <description>Effective information sharing is crucial for resolving cases efficiently. Today, we are excited to announce the launch of File Attachments for Case Management, a capability designed to enhance your case investigations with the sharing of reports, emails, screenshots, log files, and more, all in one centralized location within a case.&#160;
Key Benefits of Attachments for Case Management&#160;

Centralized Information: File attachments ensure that all relevant documents, images, and data are stored in one place. Reduce your reliance on external file storage and stop hunting through emails&#8212;everything you ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
