<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 17:01:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Utilize Microsoft Learn during exams and discover community in Security.</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/utilize-microsoft-learn-during-exams-and-discover-community-in/ba-p/3945471</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:36:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/utilize-microsoft-learn-during-exams-and-discover-community-in/ba-p/3945471</guid>
      <description>Leverage Microsoft Learn to help you complete your role-based certification exams.
&#160;
With Microsoft Learn, anyone can master core concepts at their speed and on their schedule.&#160;You can now&#160;access&#8239;Microsoft Learn&#8239;as a resource to help you complete your Microsoft Certification exams. This resource will be available in SC-100, SC-200, SC-300, SC-400, and other role-based exams in all languages.&#160;
&#160;
Here's what you need to know about this new resource:&#160;

Access to everything in the learn.microsoft.com domain except Q&amp;A and your profile.&#160;
No extra time will be added to complete the exam.&#160;
The exam t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactively secure your Google Cloud Resources with Microsoft Defender for Cloud</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/proactively-secure-your-google-cloud-resources-with-microsoft/ba-p/3946460</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:14:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/proactively-secure-your-google-cloud-resources-with-microsoft/ba-p/3946460</guid>
      <description>Introduction&#8239;&#160;
In today's digital landscape, where over 90 percent of organizations have embraced multicloud1&#160;&#160;solutions, security teams face the growing complexity of maintaining robust security controls and cloud security posture across multi-cloud environments. Microsoft Defender for Cloud&#8239;offers protection for cloud infrastructure, applications, and data providing a single contextual view of cloud risks across Azure, Amazon Web Services (AWS), and Google Cloud Platform (GCP).&#160;
&#160;
According to the Google Cloud Threat Horizons Report, credential theft accounted for over 60% of compromise fact...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
