<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 18:30:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Improve your app posture and hygiene using Microsoft Defender for Cloud Apps</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/improve-your-app-posture-and-hygiene-using-microsoft-defender/ba-p/3742361</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:27:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/improve-your-app-posture-and-hygiene-using-microsoft-defender/ba-p/3742361</guid>
      <description>In today's digital age, where Software as a Service (SaaS) has become ubiquitous, it is critical to have a line of sight into the SaaS applications being used in your organization. The challenge is managing the growing number of apps and knowing which apps may be misconfigured or unused. This leaves an open attack vector that can be easily taken advantage of by adversaries. In our recent announcement,&#160;we shared that Microsoft Defender for Cloud Apps is shifting to a comprehensive SaaS Security solution and how critical it is to implement holistic SaaS Security strategy. Strengthening app postu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering internet-facing devices using Microsoft Defender for Endpoint</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/discovering-internet-facing-devices-using-microsoft-defender-for/ba-p/3778975</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 16:52:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/discovering-internet-facing-devices-using-microsoft-defender-for/ba-p/3778975</guid>
      <description>Last year, we announced&#160;the evolution of the device inventory view in Microsoft Defender for Endpoint. The revamped device inventory view gave SOC analysts visibility into all discovered devices, counts and functional features (such as, search) that enhanced the overall user experience. To build on top of this work, we are expanding our device discovery capabilities through our existing network telemetry and RiskIQ integration. We&#8217;re thrilled to announce the ability to discover internet-facing devices is now in public preview.
&#160;
Threat actors are constantly scanning the internet to identify ex...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Windows Local Administrator Password Solution with Microsoft Entra (Azure AD)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/introducing-windows-local-administrator-password-solution-with/ba-p/1942487</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:52:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/introducing-windows-local-administrator-password-solution-with/ba-p/1942487</guid>
      <description>Howdy folks,&#8239;&#160;
&#8239;&#160;
Today we have some news I know many of you will be excited about! As part of our vision to give you comprehensive security solutions, we&#8217;ve joined forces with the Windows and Microsoft Intune teams to release a public preview of Windows Local Administrator Password Solution (LAPS) for Azure AD (which is now part of Microsoft Entra).
&#160;
I&#8217;ve asked Sandeep Deo, one of the Product Managers behind this release, to give you the low down on all these updates and explain how you can start using Windows LAPS with Microsoft Entra (Azure AD). You&#8217;ll find Sandeep&#8217;s blog post below.&#160;
&#160;
Be...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Data Studio - Connections to Azure Government</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-data-studio-connections-to-azure-government/ba-p/3786592</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 15:43:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-data-studio-connections-to-azure-government/ba-p/3786592</guid>
      <description>&#160;
Connections to Azure Government aren't automatically enabled in Azure Data Studio. This article will guide you through the process of enabling connections to Azure Government from Azure Data Studio.&#8195;
&#160;
Begin by connecting to your subscription in the Azure Government Portal. Then, navigate to Azure Active Directory &gt; Groups
Identify or create a group that will contain the users you wish to provision access for. In this article, we&#8217;ll use &#8220;MI_Admins&#8221;.
&#160;

&#160;
In Azure Portal, navigate to the Azure SQL Managed Instance or the server for the Azure SQL DB you wish to grant access to. On the networki...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft bolsters cloud-native security in Defender for Cloud with new API security capabilities</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-bolsters-cloud-native-security-in-defender-for-cloud/ba-p/3801818</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 14:40:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-bolsters-cloud-native-security-in-defender-for-cloud/ba-p/3801818</guid>
      <description>Application Programming Interfaces (APIs) power modern applications, fuel digital experiences, and enable faster business growth. APIs are at the heart of communication between users, cloud services, and data &#8211; more and more so as organizations move from monolithic to microservice based application architectures. But the interesting challenge is that APIs are loved by developers and threat actors alike. Threat actors increasingly use APIs as their primary attack vector to breach data from cloud applications, which means API security is now a critical priority for CISOs.&#160;
&#160;
To combat API securi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure AD Go Local Data Residency Goes Public Preview in Japan</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/azure-ad-go-local-data-residency-goes-public-preview-in-japan/ba-p/3751028</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 14:28:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/azure-ad-go-local-data-residency-goes-public-preview-in-japan/ba-p/3751028</guid>
      <description>Hi folks,&#160;
&#160;
Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) B2C, part of Microsoft Entra, enables organizations and individuals across the globe to achieve more by addressing their key security and privacy requirements, including the question of where your data is located. Today, we&#8217;re thrilled to announce Go Local Data Residency is in public preview for Japan.&#160;
&#160;
In Azure AD, Data Residency is determined by the country/region selected when creating a tenant. The Go Local data residency add-on is an option that enables Azure AD Premium P1 and P2 customers to purchase local data residency rights for their c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize your authentication flows with custom claims providers!</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/customize-your-authentication-flows-with-custom-claims-providers/ba-p/2464388</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 14:12:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/customize-your-authentication-flows-with-custom-claims-providers/ba-p/2464388</guid>
      <description>Howdy folks,&#160;
&#160;
I&#8217;m super excited to announce the public preview of custom claims providers for Azure Active Directory (Azure AD), now part of Microsoft Entra. &#160;
&#160;
A custom claims provider lets you call an API and map custom claims into the token during the authentication flow. The API call is made after the user has completed all their authentication challenges, and a token is about to be issued to the app.&#160;&#160;
We heard from many of you that you need to return additional claims into the tokens sent to your apps so that they could function as intended. And these claims were being sourced from ex...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three steps to master information governance in your organization</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/three-steps-to-master-information-governance-in-your/ba-p/3797815</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/three-steps-to-master-information-governance-in-your/ba-p/3797815</guid>
      <description>This month's episode of Uncovering Hidden Risks will discuss Information Governance and the industry trends we are seeing in this space. Information governance is the overall strategy for managing information at an organization. It is a discipline that spans several markets, including data governance, security, compliance, data privacy, content services, and more. Recently, these markets have begun to converge, highlighting the sometimes conflicting requirements between these disciplines.
&#160;
Joining our host Erica Toelle is our guest, Randolph Kahn. Mr. Kahn is a globally recognized leader in I...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Network Security @ RSA Conference 2023 (April 23-27)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-network-security-rsa-conference-2023-april-23-27/ba-p/3800541</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 16:48:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-network-security-rsa-conference-2023-april-23-27/ba-p/3800541</guid>
      <description>
&#160;
We&#8217;re thrilled to participate and connect with you at RSA Conference 2023 (RSAC) in San Francisco from April 23-27, 2023. Visit us throughout the week at the Microsoft booth at Moscone North Expo to engage with Microsoft product experts, experience interactive demos on network security technologies, and attend our in-booth theater sessions.
&#160;
Azure Network Security @ Microsoft Booth
Join us at the Microsoft booth for our 2 theater sessions focused on Azure Network Security:
&#160;
Secure your network infrastructure with Zero Trust, cloud-native network security | Thursday, April 27th, 10:40AM - ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Monitor: Logs Ingestion API Tips &amp; Tricks</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-monitor-logs-ingestion-api-tips-amp-tricks/ba-p/3792081</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 15:27:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-monitor-logs-ingestion-api-tips-amp-tricks/ba-p/3792081</guid>
      <description>Hello followers and welcome back to this new post of mine 
&#160;
Today I am going to share with you an interesting experience in configuring the Logs ingestion using the new API in Azure Monitor in a data collection rule created using ARM templates.
&#160;
In my previous HTTP Data Collector API in a real customer scenario post, I showed a possible use of the old HTTP Data Collector API but since things changed a lot with the release of the Azure Monitor Agent I decided to give the new Logs Ingestion API a try.
&#160;
I basically followed the Tutorial: Send data to Azure Monitor Logs using REST API (Resource...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly news - November 2022</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-november-2022/ba-p/3689841</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:28:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-november-2022/ba-p/3689841</guid>
      <description>



Microsoft 365 DefenderMonthly newsNovember 2022





This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various assets we have across our Defender products.&#160;&#160;







Legend:



Product videos

Webcast (recordings)

Docs on Microsoft

Blogs on Microsoft



GitHub

External

Product improvements

Previews / Announcements










Microsoft 365 Defender







Investigate incidents more effectively with the new attack story view in Microsoft 365 Defender.



Identity Protection alerts are now available in Microsoft 365 Defender.&#160;



(Preview) Microsoft Defender Exper...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly news - January 2023</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-january-2023/ba-p/3712287</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:28:17 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-january-2023/ba-p/3712287</guid>
      <description>



Microsoft 365 DefenderMonthly newsJanuary 2023 Edition





This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month across our Defender products. In this January edition, we are looking at all the goodness from December 2022. NEW: At the end we now include a list of the latest threat analytics reports, as well as other Microsoft security blogs for you.&#160;







Legend:



Product videos

Webcast (recordings)

Docs on Microsoft

Blogs on Microsoft



GitHub

External

Product improvements

Previews / Announcements







...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly news - February 2023</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-february-2023/ba-p/3734717</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:27:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-february-2023/ba-p/3734717</guid>
      <description>



Microsoft 365 DefenderMonthly newsFebruary 2023 Edition





This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month across our Defender products. In this edition, we are looking at all the goodness from January 2023. NEW: At the end we now include a list of the latest threat analytics reports, as well as other Microsoft security blogs for you.&#160;







Legend:



Product videos

Webcast (recordings)

Docs on Microsoft

Blogs on Microsoft



GitHub

External

Product improvements

Previews / Announcements










Micro...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly news - March 2023</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-march-2023/ba-p/3758308</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:27:05 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-march-2023/ba-p/3758308</guid>
      <description>



Microsoft 365 DefenderMonthly newsMarch 2023 Edition





This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month across our Defender products. In this edition, we are looking at all the goodness from February 2023.&#160;&#160;







Legend:



Product videos

Webcast (recordings)

Docs on Microsoft

Blogs on Microsoft



GitHub

External

Product improvements

Previews / Announcements










Microsoft 365 Defender







The virtual Ninja Show is back with Season 3.&#160;Check out the show schedule and add the episodes to your ca...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Data collaboration in Microsoft Purview data catalog with Ratings feature</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/introducing-data-collaboration-in-microsoft-purview-data-catalog/ba-p/3800375</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 21:59:01 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/introducing-data-collaboration-in-microsoft-purview-data-catalog/ba-p/3800375</guid>
      <description>Research suggests that ratings and reviews are critical in identifying trustworthy products. Customers can see these reviews across various industries and outlets, from Amazon's e-commerce platform, to TripAdvisor, and Yelp. This suggests that a similar approach can be adopted and ratings will be crucial to provide trust and confidence to users discovering data assets in Microsoft Purview data catalog for usage either in an analytical pipeline, reporting dashboard, etc.&#160;
&#160;
Imagine you are a data analyst tasked with building customer usage metrics for the last six months. Using Microsoft Purvie...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public Preview: Authenticator Lite (in Outlook)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/public-preview-authenticator-lite-in-outlook/ba-p/3773139</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 16:58:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/public-preview-authenticator-lite-in-outlook/ba-p/3773139</guid>
      <description>Two years ago, we shared that &#8220;It's Time to Hang Up on Phone Transports for Authentication.&#8221; Today, we&#8217;re adding the public preview of Authenticator Lite to the tools we are offering to help you move from text message (SMS) and voice-based authentication. Our priority is getting every user to sign in with modern strong authentication &#8211; passwordless, hardened against phishing, easy to use and adaptable to evolving attacks.&#160;
&#160;
Our top recommendation for modern strong authentication is the Authenticator, which offers the most robust security features, updated the most frequently, for free. Micros...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Onboarding your AWS/GCP environment to Microsoft Defender for Cloud with Terraform</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/onboarding-your-aws-gcp-environment-to-microsoft-defender-for/ba-p/3798664</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:37:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/onboarding-your-aws-gcp-environment-to-microsoft-defender-for/ba-p/3798664</guid>
      <description>Objective&#160;
The purpose of this article is to provide you with step-by-step guidance on how to use Terraform templates, to onboard your AWS/GCP environment to Microsoft Defender for Cloud. Terraform is an Infrastructure as Code (IaC) tool you can use to build, change, and version your public cloud infrastructure safely and efficiently. In addition to being a widely used tool, an advantage of using Terraform to onboard your environment to Defender for Cloud, is that you can use it for both AWS and GCP. &#160;Using Terraform to onboard your AWS/GCP environment to Defender for Cloud, allows you to auto...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entra Identity Governance with Entra Verified ID &#8211; Higher Fidelity Access Rights + Faster Onboarding</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/entra-identity-governance-with-entra-verified-id-higher-fidelity/ba-p/2466934</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 18:05:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/entra-identity-governance-with-entra-verified-id-higher-fidelity/ba-p/2466934</guid>
      <description>&#8239;I&#8217;m excited to announce the integration of Entra Identity Governance Entitlement Management with a very cool technology we recently introduced, Microsoft Entra Verified ID!&#160;
&#160;
If you think about what you need to onboard new users including employees, contractors, partners, or other business guests, it often includes verifying identity information and credentials. This process can be tedious and time-consuming, requiring users to fill out redundant online forms or paperwork, ultimately delaying hiring timelines and ramp-up periods.&#160;
&#160;
To ease this friction, we previously introduced custom&#160;ques...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enrich your advanced hunting experience using network layer signals from Zeek</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/enrich-your-advanced-hunting-experience-using-network-layer/ba-p/3794693</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/enrich-your-advanced-hunting-experience-using-network-layer/ba-p/3794693</guid>
      <description>In our previous blog about hunting for network signatures in Microsoft 365 Defender, we described how we used device discovery capabilities to capture some network event information in deeper detail and expose them in advanced hunting with the NetworkSignatureInspected action type. Since then we have made several developments, the most significant being the integration with Zeek. This release has expanded what is possible for generating network detections across Microsoft Defender for Endpoint. That announcement, shared examples of detections created for PrintNightmare and NTLM password sprayi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disconnected environments, proxies and Microsoft Defender for Endpoint</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/disconnected-environments-proxies-and-microsoft-defender-for/ba-p/3710502</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 16:35:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/disconnected-environments-proxies-and-microsoft-defender-for/ba-p/3710502</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Endpoint is a multi-platform cloud-based endpoint protection product that comprises multiple capabilities and features. There are many moving parts that make up Defender for Endpoint, and many of these parts require network connectivity. Disconnected and air-gapped environments can pose a challenge to deploying and configuring Defender for Endpoint. When proxies are added into the mix, interesting things can happen.&#160;&#160;This article is a part of a series of articles discussing Defender for Endpoint and disconnected environments. The other articles can be found here and here...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Monitor: Use Dynamic Thresholds in Log Alerts</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-monitor-use-dynamic-thresholds-in-log-alerts/ba-p/3792066</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 15:04:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-monitor-use-dynamic-thresholds-in-log-alerts/ba-p/3792066</guid>
      <description>Hello howdy readers&#160;
It has been a while since my last post, and I decided that the time of writing a new one will come up.
&#160;
In this new blog post I am going to explain how to use dynamic threshold in log alerts. Think for a second, that you need to create an alert that must, at the same time, apply to more than one resource and react to different thresholds.
The solution is inside the power of the Kusto Query Language or KQL.
This language offers several operators and functions that allow us to manipulate data to extract values, extend fields and compare values with thresholds.
Let&#8217;s take as...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Geo Exchange Online Admin Audit Logs</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/multi-geo-exchange-online-admin-audit-logs/ba-p/3793150</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 20:17:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/multi-geo-exchange-online-admin-audit-logs/ba-p/3793150</guid>
      <description>We&#8217;re excited to announce that Exchange admin audit logs are now available from all geo locations for Multi-Geo tenants in Office 365. This feature is only applicable for tenants utilizing Multi-Geo Capabilities in Microsoft 365 using Multi-Geo license. &#160;In a Multi-Geo environment, a Microsoft 365 Tenant consists of a Primary provisioned location (where Microsoft 365 subscription was originally provisioned) and one or more satellite locations.
&#160;

&#160;
Prior to the release of this feature, exchange admin audit events were available only for the Primary provisioned location. With the rollout of thi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New network-based detections and improved device discovery using Zeek</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/new-network-based-detections-and-improved-device-discovery-using/ba-p/3682111</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 19:44:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/new-network-based-detections-and-improved-device-discovery-using/ba-p/3682111</guid>
      <description>Organizations are finding network-based attacks becoming an increasingly popular way of infiltrating systems because they often leave minimal traces on source and target devices. At Microsoft Ignite 2022, we announced partnering with Zeek, an open-source network security monitoring platform, and its corporate sponsor, Corelight, to help security teams combat these attacks more effectively.&#160; As a result, Zeek is now integrated as a component within Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.&#160;&#160;&#160;&#160;
&#160;
The integration of Zeek into Microsoft Defender for Endpoint provides new levels of network analysis capabili...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitlocker Is Not Resuming After Reboot Count Has Been Reached</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/bitlocker-is-not-resuming-after-reboot-count-has-been-reached/ba-p/3794509</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 18:36:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/bitlocker-is-not-resuming-after-reboot-count-has-been-reached/ba-p/3794509</guid>
      <description>Hi,
&#160;
I'm Helmut Wagensonner, a Cloud Solution Architect Engineer at Microsoft. Recently, I ran into an unexpected Bitlocker behavior at a customer. It turned out that this behavior is on purpose so I thought I let you know about it, even if you may never run into it.
&#160;
BitLocker is a feature in Windows 10/11 that encrypts your device&#8217;s hard drive to protect your data from unauthorized access. However, there are some scenarios where you may need to suspend BitLocker temporarily, such as when you update your BIOS or firmware using a vendor&#8217;s update utility. When you suspend BitLocker, you can s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Entra Change Announcements &#8211; March 2023 Train</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/microsoft-entra-change-announcements-march-2023-train/ba-p/2967448</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 15:45:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/microsoft-entra-change-announcements-march-2023-train/ba-p/2967448</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone,&#160;
&#160;
Today, we're sharing our March train for feature and breaking changes. We also communicate these changes on release notes and via email. We are continuing to make it easier for our customers to manage lifecycle changes (deprecations, retirements, service breaking changes) within the new Entra admin center as well. In addition, we will be including new feature launch announcements as part of this blog post going forward so you can see both changes to existing features and new features in a single list.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
March 2023 change announcements:
&#160;
Security Improvements&#160;
Number Match...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Priva: Helping you build a privacy resilient workplace.</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-priva-helping-you-build-a-privacy-resilient-workplace/ba-p/3793313</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-priva-helping-you-build-a-privacy-resilient-workplace/ba-p/3793313</guid>
      <description>Last week, the 2023 IAPP Global Privacy Summit was held in Washington DC. There, privacy professionals and leaders from around the world came together to promote learning and awareness for data privacy. IAPP GPS served as a platform for individuals and organizations to come together to put privacy at the forefront of business practices&#8212;showcasing that the right set of tools can help meet fast-paced privacy regulatory changes.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Microsoft Priva
Microsoft Priva was launched in 2021 to help organizations in their privacy journeys. Microsoft Priva brings automated functionality to help organizat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing a new way to verify your workplace on LinkedIn with Microsoft Entra Verified ID</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/introducing-a-new-way-to-verify-your-workplace-on-linkedin-with/ba-p/3627349</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 13:52:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/introducing-a-new-way-to-verify-your-workplace-on-linkedin-with/ba-p/3627349</guid>
      <description>Today we&#8217;re excited to announce that millions of LinkedIn members will soon be able to verify their place of work with a Microsoft Entra Verified ID credential. Workplace verifications will be visible on a LinkedIn member&#8217;s profile, confirming that the work affiliations listed are accurate while serving as a signal of trust and authenticity to other members and organizations on LinkedIn.&#160;
&#160;
How to issue employee IDs that verify the workplace&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Organizations can use Verified ID to create digital employee IDs that reflect their brand and business needs in a matter of minutes. LinkedIn members ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Microsoft Secure 2023 Learn Live series is still underway! Join in real-time or watch on demand.</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/the-microsoft-secure-2023-learn-live-series-is-still-underway/ba-p/3780128</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 16:20:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/the-microsoft-secure-2023-learn-live-series-is-still-underway/ba-p/3780128</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Secure 2023&#160;may be over, but the learning continues. We have a&#160;range of learning opportunities&#160;for you that complement key topics and themes from the event, including a&#160;series of four Microsoft Secure Learn Live episodes&#160;you can join in real-time or watch on demand.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Each Learn Live episode is a live, guided experience where participants work through a single Microsoft Learn module together. Microsoft experts lead the session, providing helpful commentary and insights and answering participants&#8217; questions. It&#8217;s a great opportunity to earn badges, prepare for certifications, and ga...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Purview Information Protection in Microsoft 365 Apps - April 2023</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-purview-information-protection-in-microsoft-365-apps/ba-p/3789517</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-purview-information-protection-in-microsoft-365-apps/ba-p/3789517</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the quarterly newsletter from Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook discussing&#160;what&#8217;s&#160;new and coming soon with sensitivity labels, powered by Microsoft Purview&#160;Information Protection. We pick up&#160;where we left off in January 2023.
&#160;
From Bolt-On to Built-In: Recap
In March 2023,

We started rolling out to Current Channel the new configuration for M365 Apps that disables the AIP add-in by default, alongside a slew of new features that replace the capabilities of the add-in.

&#160;
From Bolt-On to Built-In:&#160;April 2023
Using the various feedback channels and quality signals we rely on, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retirement notification for the Azure Information Protection Unified Labeling add-in for Office</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/retirement-notification-for-the-azure-information-protection/ba-p/3791908</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/retirement-notification-for-the-azure-information-protection/ba-p/3791908</guid>
      <description>The Azure Information Protection (AIP) Unified Labeling add-in for Office has been in-market for close to eight years. In that time, it has grown in functionality and usage, becoming deeply embedded in the information protection strategy for thousands of organizations and used daily by millions of users. Since October 2019, Microsoft 365 Apps for Enterprise has been building the same functionality into Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook and has expanded sensitivity labels across Windows, Mac, Web, and Mobile for a comprehensive, consistent, and seamless experience for end-users and admins. M...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost Governance with Azure Policy</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/cost-governance-with-azure-policy/ba-p/3791888</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 23:34:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/cost-governance-with-azure-policy/ba-p/3791888</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Hi folks! My name is Felipe Binotto, Cloud Solution Architect, based in Australia.
&#160;
This post is about how you can implement Cost Governance with Azure Policy.
&#160;
I have delivered many Well-Architected Optimization Assessments and some of the policies here can help you to get closer to that Well-Architected state.
&#160;
Cost governance is an essential aspect of managing any cloud infrastructure. Azure Policy is a powerful tool that can help implement cost governance measures within your Azure environment. With Azure Policy, you can define and enforce rules to control costs, monitor us...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Information Protection SDK 1.13: Now Available!</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-information-protection-sdk-1-13-now-available/ba-p/3773479</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 20:54:06 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-information-protection-sdk-1-13-now-available/ba-p/3773479</guid>
      <description>We're pleased to announce that the Microsoft Information Protection SDK version 1.13 is now generally available via&#160;NuGet&#160;and&#160;Download Center.
&#160;
In this release of the Microsoft Information Protection SDK, we've focused on adding preview support for offline publishing and have made changes in how MIP SDK consumes Office documents and emails protected with AES in cipher block chaining (CBC) mode.
&#160;
Offline Publishing
Until now, applying protection to a file required an online call to fetch a publishing license from the rights management service. In MIP SDK 1.13, we've added public preview suppo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check This Out! (CTO!) Guide (March 2023)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/check-this-out-cto-guide-march-2023/ba-p/3787764</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/check-this-out-cto-guide-march-2023/ba-p/3787764</guid>
      <description>&#160;
Hi everyone! Brandon Wilson here once again with this month&#8217;s &#8220;Check This Out!&#8221; (CTO!) guide.
These posts are only intended to be your guide, to lead you to some content of interest, and are just a way we are trying to help our readers a bit more, whether that is learning, troubleshooting, or just finding new content sources! We will give you a bit of a taste of the blog content itself, provide you a way to get to the source content directly, and help to introduce you to some other blogs you may not be aware of that you might find helpful.
From all of us on the Core Infrastructure and Securi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying SaaS Security: Deploying Microsoft Defender for Cloud Apps in 4 steps</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/simplifying-saas-security-deploying-microsoft-defender-for-cloud/ba-p/3788360</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 20:28:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/simplifying-saas-security-deploying-microsoft-defender-for-cloud/ba-p/3788360</guid>
      <description>The Software as a Service (SaaS) landscape has evolved dramatically. The proliferation of cloud-based applications has brought significant benefits in terms of scalability, accessibility, and cost-effectiveness. However, it has also led to an increased need for organizations to secure these applications and protect their data. We understand it can be challenging to know where to begin and ensure you have protection across your entire digital estate.
&#160;
Microsoft Defender for Cloud Apps makes it simple to secure organization&#8217;s SaaS applications. It&#160;can be deployed quickly and easily, with no oth...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 State of Cloud Permissions Risks report now published</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/2023-state-of-cloud-permissions-risks-report-now-published/ba-p/1061397</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 20:37:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/2023-state-of-cloud-permissions-risks-report-now-published/ba-p/1061397</guid>
      <description>As organizations are embracing and adopting multicloud infrastructures, identity permissions have increased across three leading cloud platforms: Microsoft Azure, Amazon Web Services (AWS), and Google Cloud Platform (GPC). Although this shift brings new opportunities for innovation, it presents new permission challenges organizations have never faced before.
&#160;
Today, we&#8217;re thrilled to announce our 2023 State of Cloud Permissions Risks report. The report covers key risk findings surrounding identities and permissions across multicloud infrastructures.
&#160;

&#160;
This year we&#8217;ve found some eye-opening...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modernizing Endpoints - Installing CM Client on AADJ Device</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/modernizing-endpoints-installing-cm-client-on-aadj-device/ba-p/3775756</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 17:00:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/modernizing-endpoints-installing-cm-client-on-aadj-device/ba-p/3775756</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
In this blog we will discuss a specific use case that I came across while working with a Community College. The college wanted to simplify their Windows provisioning. They had a lot of apps built in their ConfigMgr environment. This is when we took advantage of the co-management capability offered by Windows Autopilot in connecting a pure Azure AD joined PC with ConfigMgr without using Cloud Management Gateway (CMG) or Hybrid Domain Join.
&#160;
The other reason I wanted to write this blog is, searching the internet for Autopilot and co-management, brings results using CMG. Here I wan...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Virtual Ninja Show: Season 3 Recap!</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/the-virtual-ninja-show-season-3-recap/ba-p/3788035</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 12:39:24 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/the-virtual-ninja-show-season-3-recap/ba-p/3788035</guid>
      <description>Season 3 of the Ninja Show has come to a close! Spanning the month of March, we were incredibly grateful to have such talented experts on with us to share their knowledge about many of the products, key features, and impressive capabilities within Microsoft 365 Defender.&#160;
&#160;
This season covered content extensively - across nearly our entire repertoire of Microsoft 365 Defender products. Featured highlights consist of our very first Microsoft Sentinel episode, a Microsoft Defender for Identity and Defender for Endpoint Better Together conversation, and numerous deep dives into the best practices...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public preview: Programmatically interact with Microsoft Purview workflows using APIs and SDKs</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/public-preview-programmatically-interact-with-microsoft-purview/ba-p/3786519</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 17:26:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/public-preview-programmatically-interact-with-microsoft-purview/ba-p/3786519</guid>
      <description>To increase our developer experience&#160;landscape and to allow customers to interact and extend Microsoft Purview functionality using software technologies and tools in their organization, we are happy to announce that REST APIs and SDKs for workflow data plane&#160;in public preview. Software engineers or developers in your organization can now leverage these APIs/SDKs to programmatically create or update a workflow, submit a workflow, approve or reject an action, update or re-assign an approval or task action, list or cancel workflow runs, and more.
&#160;
In order to use any Microsoft Purview data plane...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncover the latest cloud data security capabilities from Microsoft Defender for Cloud</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/uncover-the-latest-cloud-data-security-capabilities-from/ba-p/3785632</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 16:05:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/uncover-the-latest-cloud-data-security-capabilities-from/ba-p/3785632</guid>
      <description>As digital transformation accelerates, many organizations are moving their data to the cloud at an exponential rate, taking advantage of the cost and operational efficiencies cloud deployments offer. The dynamic and complex nature of an organization's cloud data estate &#8211; storage and database resources, where data is stored and processed &#8211; along with the increased multicloud adoption and cloud-native application development, have multiplied the data security blind spots for security teams.&#160;
&#160;
As a result, security teams often lack comprehensive visibility into their cloud data estate, leaving o...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defender for Endpoint and disconnected environments. Cloud-centric networking decisions</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/defender-for-endpoint-and-disconnected-environments-cloud/ba-p/3786540</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/defender-for-endpoint-and-disconnected-environments-cloud/ba-p/3786540</guid>
      <description>About this article
This article is part of a group of articles regarding Defender for Endpoint and disconnected environments. The first two articles can be found here and here.
&#160;
The objective of this article, along with the two previous articles, is to provide you with a better understanding of Defender for Endpoint and how it works in a disconnected environment. This requires a mental shift in our understanding of what &#8220;risk&#8221; means with a cloud-first product.
&#160;
Looking at how Defender for Endpoint is designed we can make a few observations:
&#160;

Defender for Endpoint is a cloud-based EDR and A...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly news - April 2023</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-april-2023/ba-p/3785877</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 19:52:15 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/monthly-news-april-2023/ba-p/3785877</guid>
      <description>



Microsoft 365 DefenderMonthly newsApril 2023 Edition





This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month across our Defender products. In this edition, we are looking at all the goodness from March 2023.&#160;&#160;







Legend:



Product videos

Webcast (recordings)

Docs on Microsoft

Blogs on Microsoft



GitHub

External

Product improvements

Previews / Announcements










Microsoft 365 Defender







Season 3 of the virtual Ninja Show&#160;now on-demand. 10 episodes for you to watch either on the show page or we...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Wins to Strengthen Your Azure AD Security</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/quick-wins-to-strengthen-your-azure-ad-security/ba-p/3767905</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 16:39:33 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/quick-wins-to-strengthen-your-azure-ad-security/ba-p/3767905</guid>
      <description>Every organization strives to reduce the attack surface of their infrastructure to make it secure and reliable.&#8239;&#160;
&#160;
As team members of the Microsoft Global Compromise Recovery Security Practice (CRSP), we&#8217;ve seen time and time again that by improving the security posture to make compromise more difficult than average, low-skill attackers usually give up quickly and move to the next target.&#160;
&#160;
With the changing cybersecurity landscapes,&#8239;Identity is the new security perimeter&#8239;and we often hear that a compromised user was the cause of a catastrophic cyber-attack.&#8239;&#8239;&#160;
&#8239;&#8239;&#160;
While talking about identi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Purview DevOps policies for Azure SQL Database is now generally available</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-purview-devops-policies-for-azure-sql-database-is-now/ba-p/3775885</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-purview-devops-policies-for-azure-sql-database-is-now/ba-p/3775885</guid>
      <description>In a prior blog, we announced&#160;the General Availability (GA) of the Microsoft Purview DevOps policies integration with SQL Server 2022 (Arc-enabled). Today, we are launching&#160;DevOps policies for Azure SQL Database into GA.
&#160;
In a nutshell, you can use DevOps policies to provision access to database system metadata at-scale, securely and inexpensively. Who needs that access? Your internal IT/DevOps personnel or your external contractors that are tasked with monitoring health, tuning performance, and reviewing audit information in SQL systems.
&#160;
With DevOps policies, you can now manage access to S...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Offerings: Well-Architected Cost Optimization Implementation</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/customer-offerings-well-architected-cost-optimization/ba-p/3771569</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 12:59:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/customer-offerings-well-architected-cost-optimization/ba-p/3771569</guid>
      <description>&#160;
Hi everyone! Brandon Wilson (Cloud Solution Architect/Engineer) here to follow up on the post I authored previously for the Well-Architected Cost Optimization Assessment offering, with another customer offering we have known as the Well-Architected Cost Optimization Implementation. This offering can be considered as a continuation/&#8221;part 2&#8221; of sorts for the Well-Architected Cost Optimization Assessment, where the goal is to help you implement some of the findings relating to Azure Reservations, Azure Savings Plans, Azure Hybrid Benefits, along with cleaning up some of that cloud waste sitting...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly news - April 2023</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/monthly-news-april-2023/ba-p/3778634</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 13:30:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/monthly-news-april-2023/ba-p/3778634</guid>
      <description>







Microsoft Defender for Cloud
Monthly news
April 2023 Edition









This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month. In this edition, we are looking at all the goodness from March 2023.







Legend:



Product videos

Webcasts (recordings)

Docs on Microsoft

Blogs on Microsoft



GitHub

External content

Product improvements

Announcements










&#160;Microsoft Defender for Cloud



Watch a new episode of the Defender for Cloud in the Field show to learn about&#160;the principles of Zero Trust, the importanc...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing and Optimizing Your Azure Hybrid Benefit Usage (With Tools!)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/managing-and-optimizing-your-azure-hybrid-benefit-usage-with/ba-p/3783541</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 12:34:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/managing-and-optimizing-your-azure-hybrid-benefit-usage-with/ba-p/3783541</guid>
      <description>As more businesses shift their operations to the cloud, one of the challenges they face is optimizing licensing costs for their virtual machines (VMs) in the cloud. Microsoft's Azure Hybrid Benefit (AHUB) is a licensing benefit that can help businesses save money on their Azure VMs by using their existing on-premises licenses. However, in some cases, it can be hard to keep track of which VMs have the benefit enabled, how to prioritize VMs to have AHUB and how many CPU Cores are being consumed in the environment.
With this challenge in mind, I have developed this Workbook that will help you man...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom attributes for Azure Active Directory Domain Services now in Public Preview</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/custom-attributes-for-azure-active-directory-domain-services-now/ba-p/3778049</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 21:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/custom-attributes-for-azure-active-directory-domain-services-now/ba-p/3778049</guid>
      <description>Howdy folks!&#8239;&#160;
&#8239;&#8239;&#160;
Today I&#8217;m excited to share a new enhancement for your Azure Active Directory Domain Services (Azure AD DS) instances.&#160;&#160;

&#160;
&#160;This new capability provides you with the ability to use Custom Attributes in your managed domains.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Custom Attributes (Public Preview)&#160;
For various reasons, companies often will not or cannot modify code for legacy apps. These legacy apps may have utilized custom attributes, such as a custom employee id in their directory and leveraged these attributes in their app LDAP calls. Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) stores these extended user attributes (...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage the most critical data security risks inside your organization with intelligent automation</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/manage-the-most-critical-data-security-risks-inside-your/ba-p/3778245</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 16:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/manage-the-most-critical-data-security-risks-inside-your/ba-p/3778245</guid>
      <description>Data security incidents are commonly caused by insider actions, accounting for nearly 35% of all unauthorized incidents*. Even the strongest cybersecurity programs can be undermined by insiders who either intentionally or unintentionally compromise an enterprise. Insider risks such as data leakage and data theft are particularly common, and it has become crucial for all organizations to address, especially in today&#8217;s hybrid work environment. Gartner&#174; predicts, &#8220;By 2025, insider risk will cause 50% of organizations to adopt formal programs to manage it, up from 10% today.&#8221;**.
&#160;
Combating evolvi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Office 2016\2019 to Microsoft 365 Apps</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/migrating-from-office-2016-2019-to-microsoft-365-apps/ba-p/3765464</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 12:51:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/migrating-from-office-2016-2019-to-microsoft-365-apps/ba-p/3765464</guid>
      <description>Note:
While we normally don&#8217;t cover this type of content on the Core Infrastructure and Security Blog, we thought this was important enough to provide our readers in order to support many Microsoft security capabilities.
&#160;
Introduction
Hello everyone, I am Dave Guenthner, a Senior FastTrack Architect (FTA) at Microsoft. The purpose of this blog is to share a concern from multiple customers and provide suggestions and reference documentation for resolution. &#160;The issue is that after October 10, 2023, older perpetual versions of Office 2016 and Office 2019, which are no longer in mainstream suppo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why De-privileging?</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/why-de-privileging/ba-p/3779519</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 23:01:18 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/why-de-privileging/ba-p/3779519</guid>
      <description>This post starts a series explaining why we at Microsoft Security Services for Incident Response recommend some of our favorite protections. Our first post in the series talks about identity hygiene.
&#160;
If you&#8217;re new to our services, we&#8217;re a team of cyber-security experts at Microsoft who help companies get global response with investigation and recovery by applying proven practices against various types of attacks before, during and after a security incident. You&#8217;ll learn more about us and what to do in our page here: https://aka.ms/MicrosoftIR
&#160;
Our goal with this post is to highlight the imp...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A proactive and comprehensive approach to data security with Microsoft Purview Data Loss Prevention</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/a-proactive-and-comprehensive-approach-to-data-security-with/ba-p/3779248</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 22:24:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/a-proactive-and-comprehensive-approach-to-data-security-with/ba-p/3779248</guid>
      <description>In today&#8217;s modern workplace data security incidents can happen any time as users collaborate on data across a myriad networks, devices, and applications. And the volume of data, people who interact with the data, and activities around the data are all constantly changing. All of this means that the data security risks are increasing exponentially, and many organizations are struggling to keep up given their limited resources. This comes at a time when a recent Microsoft study showed that two in five security leaders feel at extreme risk due to cybersecurity staff shortage [1]. Organizations ar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Configuration Manager Site Server OS &#8211; In-place Upgrade Reference</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-in-place-upgrade/ba-p/3770615</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 18:46:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-in-place-upgrade/ba-p/3770615</guid>
      <description>Hello!
&#160;
My name is Herbert Fuchs and together with other members of the Customer Success Unit and the Customer Service &amp; Support Organization we want to help our Customers with This Blog-Series. We gathered information and put
our field and support experience into this. Special thanks to our contributors, reviewers and content-writers, Wilhelm Kocher, Anthony Fontanez, Emilian Bucur, Pavel Yurenev, Anderson Cassimiro and Madalina Zamfir.
&#160;
In this Blog we want to explain what is necessary to change the Operating System of a Server which hosts the Configuration Manager through an In-place Upgr...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved experience for managing the default Azure security policies</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/improved-experience-for-managing-the-default-azure-security/ba-p/3776522</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 12:52:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/improved-experience-for-managing-the-default-azure-security/ba-p/3776522</guid>
      <description>Introduction
To improve your overall security posture, you have to implement security recommendations for your environment.
The Microsoft Cloud Security Benchmark is a Microsoft-authored set of guidelines that are being adopted as the default for security and compliance best practices based on common compliance frameworks.
There are currently multiple options and advanced capabilities for managing security recommendations in Azure. It is often heard from customers that security recommendations need to be managed more effectively, as well as that basic operations need to be performed to fine tu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Collaboration Security for Microsoft Teams</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/announcing-collaboration-security-for-microsoft-teams/ba-p/3780487</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 23:27:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/announcing-collaboration-security-for-microsoft-teams/ba-p/3780487</guid>
      <description>Since 2020, remote work has fundamentally changed the way organizations operate. 66% of businesses worldwide now rely on a hybrid work model, and as a result adoption of collaboration platforms like&#160;Microsoft Teams have surged. Today, 270 million users use Teams to communicate and be productive, making it indispensable to effective collaboration. &#160;
However, the growing number of users has also made a new target for adversaries trying to gain access to an organizations&#8217; sensitive data and operations. Attacks like phishing and ransomware that for decades have primarily used email as an entry poi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Defender CSPM GA &amp; new data security capabilities in Microsoft Defender for Cloud</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/announcing-defender-cspm-ga-amp-new-data-security-capabilities/ba-p/3781013</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 21:01:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/announcing-defender-cspm-ga-amp-new-data-security-capabilities/ba-p/3781013</guid>
      <description>With the increasing complexity around the development and adoption of cloud applications, organizations worry about vulnerabilities in code getting deployed, critical misconfigurations, overprivileged access to cloud infrastructure, and evolving threats that can cause sensitive data exposure.
&#160;
Microsoft is leading the next chapter of comprehensive multicloud security so organizations can start secure with proactive posture hardening and stay secure with advanced threat protection across cloud apps, infrastructure, and data.
&#160;
Recognized by Gartner as a Representative Vendor in its 2023 Market...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamline your multi-cloud assessments with Microsoft Purview Compliance Manager</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/streamline-your-multi-cloud-assessments-with-microsoft-purview/ba-p/3780529</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:47:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/streamline-your-multi-cloud-assessments-with-microsoft-purview/ba-p/3780529</guid>
      <description>Data has become the lifeblood of every business, but with the shift to hybrid work and unprecedented levels of digital transformation, an organization&#8217;s data now lives outside of the traditional borders of business. Over 30% of decision makers do not know where or what their sensitive business-critical data is[1], making it impossible for organizations to protect that data, close exposure gaps, or comply with regulatory requirements.
&#160;
Just like seatbelts and speed limits took some time to protect passengers riding vehicles, privacy regulations are just catching up to the pace of digital trans...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn how Microsoft Purview Information Protection discovers and protects your most sensitive data</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/learn-how-microsoft-purview-information-protection-discovers-and/ba-p/3777181</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/learn-how-microsoft-purview-information-protection-discovers-and/ba-p/3777181</guid>
      <description>Did you know that 88% of organizations lack the confidence to prevent sensitive data loss?1 Data discovery and classification are the important first steps for organizations who want to better protect sensitive PII and corporate intellectual property; you can&#8217;t prevent data loss with policies if the right files aren&#8217;t correctly labeled and aren&#8217;t protected to begin with.
&#160;
With Microsoft Purview, our goal is to provide a built-in, intelligent, unified, and extensible solution to protect sensitive data across your digital estate. This includes Microsoft clouds such as Microsoft 365 and Azure, a...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify the lifecycle of sensitive data</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/simplify-the-lifecycle-of-sensitive-data/ba-p/3780362</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/simplify-the-lifecycle-of-sensitive-data/ba-p/3780362</guid>
      <description>Data security continues to be top of mind for business leaders. Data security continues to be top of mind for business leaders. The high data breach costs concern everyone, and these costs keep increasing each year. Let&#8217;s look at some of the data from 2022[1].
&#160;

The worldwide average data breach cost was 4.35 million dollars per breach. This cost increased by almost 13% from 2020.
The average cost of destructive attacks is even higher. A destructive attack involves encrypting files, deleting data, or executing malicious code. The average cost of a destructive breach in 2022 was 5.12 million d...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Accelerator: Microsoft Secure &amp; Microsoft Intune Suite - April 11-13</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/tech-accelerator-microsoft-secure-amp-microsoft-intune-suite/ba-p/3779907</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 18:10:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/tech-accelerator-microsoft-secure-amp-microsoft-intune-suite/ba-p/3779907</guid>
      <description>We're so excited to announce the Microsoft Tech Accelerator, coming to you live April 11-13, 2023. This virtual event is focused on providing organizations and IT professionals with technical depth so they can use our products successfully. We'll also feature a closer look at everything that was presented at Microsoft Secure. Join us for three days of demos, technical deep dives, and, of course, everyone's favorite &#8211; Ask Microsoft Anything (AMA).
All sessions will be streamed live on the Microsoft Tech Community, Twitter, and YouTube. Tune in, ask ALL the questions, skill up, and have fun. Reg...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to configure Security Events collection with Azure Monitor Agent</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/how-to-configure-security-events-collection-with-azure-monitor/ba-p/3770719</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 16:42:47 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/how-to-configure-security-events-collection-with-azure-monitor/ba-p/3770719</guid>
      <description>Although Microsoft Defender for Servers (part of the Microsoft Defender for Cloud suite) does not rely on security events collection to provide its protection capabilities, customers may want to collect this valuable data to bring additional context to their server security investigations or alerts. For this reason, Defender for Servers Plan 2 users benefit from a 500-MB free data ingestion allowance (per day, per server) into Log Analytics, as long as the Defender for Servers Plan 2 is also enabled at the Log Analytics Workspace level.
&#160;
Security events collection (for Windows systems only) i...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Upgrade/Change the Operating System Which Hosts Microsoft Configuration Manager</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/how-to-upgrade-change-the-operating-system-which-hosts-microsoft/ba-p/3765523</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 11:11:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/how-to-upgrade-change-the-operating-system-which-hosts-microsoft/ba-p/3765523</guid>
      <description>Hello!
&#160;
My name is Herbert Fuchs and together with other members of the Customer Success Unit and the Customer Service &amp; Support Organization we want to help our Customers with This Blog-Series. We gathered information and put&#160;our field and support experience into this. Special thanks to our contributors, reviewers and content-writers, Wilhelm Kocher, Anthony Fontanez, Emilian Bucur, Pavel Yurenev, Anderson Cassimiro and Madalina Zamfir.
&#160;
So, what's the story - you implemented a well running ConfigMgr-Environment. New Solutions to deploy, changes in the Organizations, new Features implemente...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Configuration Manager Site Server OS &#8211; Side-by-Side Migration Reference</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-side-by-side/ba-p/3770673</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-side-by-side/ba-p/3770673</guid>
      <description>Hello!
&#160;
My name is Herbert Fuchs and together with other members of the Customer Success Unit and the Customer Service &amp; Support Organization we want to help our Customers with This Blog-Series. We gathered information and put
our field and support experience into this. Special thanks to our contributors, reviewers and content-writers, Wilhelm Kocher, Anthony Fontanez, Emilian Bucur, Pavel Yurenev, Anderson Cassimiro and Madalina Zamfir.
&#160;
In this Blog we want to explain what is necessary to change the Operating System of a Server which hosts the Configuration Manager by a Side-by-Side Migrat...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Entra Updates You May Have Missed</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/microsoft-entra-updates-you-may-have-missed/ba-p/2967449</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 17:42:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/microsoft-entra-updates-you-may-have-missed/ba-p/2967449</guid>
      <description>The second quarter of the Microsoft year saw several security feature updates for Microsoft Entra, as well as the announcement of general availability in a wide number of capability areas throughout the security space to help you improve your organization&#8217;s security posture.&#160;
&#160;
In case you missed the announcements as they happened or want to quickly peruse an all-up listing of what Microsoft has added, check out the comprehensive list below. We&#8217;ve organized these updates by capability area, making your area of interest easy to find and review:&#160;
&#160;&#160;
Identity security / protecting Identities&#160;

Co...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leverage Azure Recovery Services Vault for rapid recovery</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/leverage-azure-recovery-services-vault-for-rapid-recovery/ba-p/3777905</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 17:26:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/leverage-azure-recovery-services-vault-for-rapid-recovery/ba-p/3777905</guid>
      <description>Sometimes success in life depends on little things that seem easy. So easy that they are often overlooked or underestimated for some reason.&#160;This also applies to life in IT. For example, just think about this simple question: "Do you have a tested and documented Active Directory disaster recovery plan?&#8221;
&#160;
This is a question we, as Microsoft Global Compromise Recovery Security Practice, ask our customers whenever we engage in a Compromise Recovery project. The aim of these projects is to evict the attacker from compromised environments by revoking their access, thereby restoring confidence in t...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Configuration Manager Site Server OS &#8211; High Availability Reference</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-high-availability/ba-p/3770649</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-high-availability/ba-p/3770649</guid>
      <description>Hello!
&#160;
My name is Herbert Fuchs and together with other members of the Customer Success Unit and the Customer Service &amp; Support Organization we want to help our Customers with This Blog-Series. We gathered information and put
our field and support experience into this. Special thanks to our contributors, reviewers and content-writers, Wilhelm Kocher, Anthony Fontanez, Emilian Bucur, Pavel Yurenev, Anderson Cassimiro and Madalina Zamfir.
&#160;
In this Blog we want to explain what is necessary to change the Operating System of a Server which hosts the Configuration Manager through the High Availab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monthly news - March 2023</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/monthly-news-march-2023/ba-p/3758712</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 20:25:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/monthly-news-march-2023/ba-p/3758712</guid>
      <description>







Microsoft Defender for Cloud
Monthly news
March 2023 Edition









This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month. In this edition, we are looking at all the goodness from February 2023.







Legend:



Product videos

Webcasts (recordings)

Docs on Microsoft

Blogs on Microsoft



GitHub

External content

Product improvements

Announcements










&#160;Microsoft Defender for Cloud



Watch two new episodes of the Defender for Cloud in the Field show about Defender for Servers and Governance capabiliti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure WAF Tuning for Web Applications</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-waf-tuning-for-web-applications/ba-p/3776133</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 17:51:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-waf-tuning-for-web-applications/ba-p/3776133</guid>
      <description>Azure Web Application Firewall provides a comprehensive solution for protecting web applications from various types of application attacks, ensuring high availability and optimal performance. It is critical to configure WAF in such a way as to reduce the likelihood of false positives while still providing sufficient protection against actual threats.
False positives occur when a Web Application Firewall (WAF) erroneously detects legitimate web traffic as malicious and subsequently denies access. For instance, an HTTP request that poses no threat may trigger WAF to classify it as an SQL injecti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud native Data Loss Prevention: the future of data security</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/cloud-native-data-loss-prevention-the-future-of-data-security/ba-p/3771548</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/cloud-native-data-loss-prevention-the-future-of-data-security/ba-p/3771548</guid>
      <description>Data loss prevention (DLP) is a layer of an organization's data security strategy. It helps protect sensitive data by preventing users from inappropriately sharing it with people who shouldn't have it. Forward-thinking organizations are seeking to future-proof their DLP strategy with a comprehensive solution that scales across all applications, services, endpoints, and platforms.
In this month&#8217;s episode of Uncovering Hidden Risks, we discuss some recent DLP research and what's coming up in this space. Microsoft spoke to more than 300 data and compliance professionals to create the whitepaper &#8220;...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Microsoft cloud security benchmark v1 (General Availability)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/announcing-microsoft-cloud-security-benchmark-v1-general/ba-p/3763013</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 12:03:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/announcing-microsoft-cloud-security-benchmark-v1-general/ba-p/3763013</guid>
      <description>Since its first introduction in 2019, the&#160;Azure Security Benchmark (ASB) has been widely used by our customers to secure their Azure environments, especially as a toolkit for Azure security implementation planning and helping report compliance on multiple regulatory standards. As the successor of ASB, today we are announcing the general availability&#160;the&#160;Microsoft cloud security benchmark v1
&#160;
The Microsoft cloud security benchmark (MCSB) v1 is an expanded and enhanced version from Azure Security Benchmark v3 with a new layer of multicloud security guidance. Currently, a full set of security gu...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft awarded Best Advanced Protection for Corporate and Consumer Users by AV-TEST</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/microsoft-awarded-best-advanced-protection-for-corporate-and/ba-p/3765332</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 18:04:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/microsoft-awarded-best-advanced-protection-for-corporate-and/ba-p/3765332</guid>
      <description>Antivirus software has been a staple investment for protecting enterprise and consumer endpoints alike from cyberthreats. As these attacks have evolved from sending funny messages across the screen of your personal desktop to now holding entire organizations to ransom with the click of a button, a traditional, signature-based approach is no longer good enough to detect and respond to modern day threats.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Today Microsoft is pleased to announce that AV-TEST has awarded Microsoft Best Advanced Protection 2022 for both Corporate Users and Consumer Users categories. After a year of extensive lab...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity Innovation for a More Secure Nation</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/identity-innovation-for-a-more-secure-nation/ba-p/2365670</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 17:14:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/identity-innovation-for-a-more-secure-nation/ba-p/2365670</guid>
      <description>With more than 1000 identity attacks occurring each second1, government agencies are tasked with serving the public amidst the most challenging cybersecurity environment in history. Protecting the freedom of citizens makes them a prime target for bad actors across the cyberthreat ecosystem, from nation-state attacks on our infrastructure to identity compromise. Expanding security threats put federal agencies and their most critical data at risk.&#160;
&#160;
With recent innovations like phishing-resistant multifactor authentication (MFA) from Azure Active Directory - part of Microsoft Entra - government...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving efficiency of your eDiscovery workflows with Microsoft Purview</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/improving-efficiency-of-your-ediscovery-workflows-with-microsoft/ba-p/3770423</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/improving-efficiency-of-your-ediscovery-workflows-with-microsoft/ba-p/3770423</guid>
      <description>The demands of digital transformation are leading organizations to increasingly rely on collaboration platforms, resulting in a surge of Electronically Stored Information (ESI). This trend presents additional challenges for eDiscovery teams to sift through the vast amounts of data for investigations and litigations. According to Statista, the size of the digital universe is expected to reach 180 zettabytes by 2025, further compounding this challenge. Moreover, global economic headwinds are putting pressure on organizations to find ways to do more with less, causing tighter budgets and resource...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decision Flow to Estimate Pod Spread on AKS</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/decision-flow-to-estimate-pod-spread-on-aks/ba-p/3761125</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/decision-flow-to-estimate-pod-spread-on-aks/ba-p/3761125</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), the concept of pod spread is important to ensure that pods are distributed efficiently across nodes in a cluster. This helps to optimize resource utilization, increase application performance, and maintain high availability.
&#160;
This article outlines a decision-making process for estimating the number of Pods running on an AKS cluster. We will look at&#160;pod distribution across designated node pools,&#160;distribution based on&#160;pod-to-pod dependencies and&#160;distribution&#160;where pod or node affinities are not specified. Finally, we explore the impact of pod spre...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancements to Azure WAF for Application Gateway now in General Availability</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/enhancements-to-azure-waf-for-application-gateway-now-in-general/ba-p/3764840</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:59:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/enhancements-to-azure-waf-for-application-gateway-now-in-general/ba-p/3764840</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Azure Web Application Firewall (WAF) on Azure Application Gateway provides centralized protection for your web applications against common vulnerabilities and exploits. Web applications are increasingly targeted by malicious attacks that vulnerabilities. SQL Injection (SQLi) and Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) are examples of some well-known attacks. Preventing such attacks in application code can be challenging and may require rigorous maintenance, patching, and monitoring at many layers of the application topology. A centralized web application firewall helps make security management...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#8217;t miss us at Microsoft Secure &amp; Gartner IAM</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/don-t-miss-us-at-microsoft-secure-amp-gartner-iam/ba-p/2520437</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 21:13:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/don-t-miss-us-at-microsoft-secure-amp-gartner-iam/ba-p/2520437</guid>
      <description>Event season is approaching! Our team is looking forward to seeing you all at Gartner Identity &amp; Access Management (IAM) and Microsoft Secure this month! Check out our identity sessions below:
&#160;
Gartner Identity &amp; Access Management
Microsoft will be participating in Gartner IAM March 20-22 in Grapevine, TX. While onsite Microsoft will demo the latest innovations in Microsoft Entra, and host customers during onsite meetings. Don&#8217;t miss us at booth #301!
&#160;
Pamela Dingle, Partner Director of Microsoft Identity Standards, will deliver a solution provider session during the event.&#160;In this session, ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Configuration Manager Site Server OS &#8211; Disaster Recovery Reference</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-disaster-recovery/ba-p/3765562</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/change-configuration-manager-site-server-os-disaster-recovery/ba-p/3765562</guid>
      <description>Hello!
&#160;
My name is Herbert Fuchs and together with other members of the Customer Success Unit and the Customer Service &amp; Support Organization we want to help our Customers with This Blog-Series. We gathered information and put our field and support experience into this. Special thanks to our contributors, reviewers and content-writers, Wilhelm Kocher, Anthony Fontanez, Emilian Bucur, Pavel Yurenev, Anderson Cassimiro and Madalina Zamfir.
&#160;
In this Blog we want to explain what is necessary to change the Operating System for a Server which host the Configuration Manager by a Disaster Recovery P...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPv6 Coming to Azure AD</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/ipv6-coming-to-azure-ad/ba-p/2967451</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 21:07:57 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/ipv6-coming-to-azure-ad/ba-p/2967451</guid>
      <description>***UPDATE***
&#160;
What does my organization have to do?
&#160;
If you have public IPv6 addresses representing your network, take the actions that are described in the following sections as soon as possible.
&#160;
For example: Some organizations have a Conditional Access policy that blocks access to specific applications from outside a trusted named location that represents their public network addresses. This named location contains the IPv4 addresses that are owned by the customer, but it might not include the public IPv6 addresses that represent the customer network.
&#160;
If customers don't update their na...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Defender PoC Series &#8211; Defender CSPM</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-defender-poc-series-defender-cspm/ba-p/3768651</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 14:59:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-defender-poc-series-defender-cspm/ba-p/3768651</guid>
      <description>Introduction&#160;
&#160;
This Microsoft Defender for Cloud PoC Series provides guidelines on how to perform a proof of concept for specific Microsoft Defender plans. For a more holistic approach where you need to validate Microsoft&#8239;Defender for Cloud and Microsoft Defender plans, please read&#8239;How to Effectively Perform an Microsoft Defender for Cloud PoC&#8239;article.&#8239;&#160;
&#160;
Cloud Security Posture Management provides organizations with a centralized view of their cloud security posture, allowing them to quickly identify and respond to security risks, ensures compliance, and allows for continuous monitoring and ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Azure DDoS Solution for Microsoft Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/new-azure-ddos-solution-for-microsoft-sentinel/ba-p/3732013</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 11:28:22 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/new-azure-ddos-solution-for-microsoft-sentinel/ba-p/3732013</guid>
      <description>Written in collaboration with Amir Dahan
&#160;
Introduction
Cybercriminals demonstrate increasingly sophisticated tactics using DDoS attacks as multi-purpose tool. While DDoS attacks are commonly used to take down critical systems, applications, and infrastructure, they also serve adversaries for extortion and political or ideological motives. The crown jewel is using DDoS attacks as a smokescreen to conceal data breaches while the attention is directed to the attack. By overwhelming the targeted website or application with a large amount of traffic, the attackers can exploit vulnerabilities and s...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Block Blob Backup</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/automating-block-blob-backup/ba-p/3767274</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:51:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/automating-block-blob-backup/ba-p/3767274</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Hi folks! My name is Felipe Binotto, Cloud Solution Architect, based in Australia.
&#160;
This post is about how you can automate the backup of Block Blob Storage using Azure Backup Vault (not to be confused with Azure Recovery Service Vault). I specifically mention Block Blob because append and page blobs are not supported.
&#160;
By automating the backup process of your Block Blob Storage, you can rest assured that your data is safe and secure in case of unexpected data loss.
&#160;
Before we start, let us look at the solution&#8217;s high-level design.
&#160;
High-Level Design
The following is a similar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Respond to threats in near real-time with custom detections</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/respond-to-threats-in-near-real-time-with-custom-detections/ba-p/3761243</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/respond-to-threats-in-near-real-time-with-custom-detections/ba-p/3761243</guid>
      <description>Today we are excited to announce the public preview of near real-time custom detections in Microsoft 365 Defender. This new frequency will allow you to respond to threats faster with automated responses and gain valuable time in stopping attacks and protecting your organization.
&#160;
Automation is key to keeping up with attackers 
While Microsoft&#8217;s eXtended Detection and Response (XDR) solution helps prioritize response activities and provides a unified experience that allows for more effective investigation at the incident level, the increasing volume and speed of sophisticated attacks remains c...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Field Tips for AKS Storage Provisioning</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/field-tips-for-aks-storage-provisioning/ba-p/3761105</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:33:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/field-tips-for-aks-storage-provisioning/ba-p/3761105</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In an Azure Kubernetes (AKS) cluster, Pods can access physical storage resources such as disks or volumes using Persistent Volumes (PV). To use these resources, Pods need to make a Persistent Volume Claim (PVC), which requests a specific amount of storage from a storage class. This claim can then be matched to an available Persistent Volume. Azure offers several storage solutions that can be used to provision Persistent Volumes in an AKS cluster.
&#160;
This article will provide real-world guidance on securely using Container Storage Interface (CSI) drivers to provision Azure File Shar...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting and remediating command and control attacks at the network layer</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/detecting-and-remediating-command-and-control-attacks-at-the/ba-p/3650607</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 15:35:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/detecting-and-remediating-command-and-control-attacks-at-the/ba-p/3650607</guid>
      <description>Overview
&#160;
Update -&#160;11/10/2022 -&#160;Network Protection command and control (C2) detection and remediation capabilities are now generally available in Microsoft Defender for Endpoint.
&#160;
We are excited to announce the general availability of Network Protection command and control (C2) detection and remediation capabilities in Microsoft Defender for Endpoint. These enhancements will help improve the time it takes security operations (SecOps) teams to pinpoint and respond to malicious network threats looking to compromise the endpoint.
&#160;
Attackers often compromise existing internet-connected servers ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mobile Threat Defense capabilities for Android &amp; iOS</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/new-mobile-threat-defense-capabilities-for-android-amp-ios/ba-p/3611529</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 15:33:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/new-mobile-threat-defense-capabilities-for-android-amp-ios/ba-p/3611529</guid>
      <description>Update: As of 9/20/22, privacy controls and web protection configuration for Android MAM are now generally available.
&#160;
Microsoft Defender for Endpoint for Android and iOS helps protect organizations and enterprise users by safeguarding their mobile devices from cyber threats. As the threat landscape evolves, our journey in providing the most complete and robust Mobile Threat Defense solution for our customers continues.
&#160;
Taking our next step on this journey, we are excited to announce a handful of new features that are generally available: Privacy Controls, Optional Permissions and Disable W...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XDR attack disruption in action &#8211; Defending against a recent BEC attack</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/xdr-attack-disruption-in-action-defending-against-a-recent-bec/ba-p/3749822</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 21:33:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/xdr-attack-disruption-in-action-defending-against-a-recent-bec/ba-p/3749822</guid>
      <description>The ever-growing volume of advanced cybersecurity attacks challenges even the most advanced Security Operations (SOC) teams. To help SOC teams address these challenges, Microsoft 365 Defender can now automatically disrupt advanced attacks like ransomware and BEC campaigns. It uses high-confidence eXtended Detection and Response (XDR) signals across endpoints, identities, email, and SaaS apps to stop attack progression and limit the impact to organizations.
&#160;
While in Private Preview, Microsoft 365 Defender disrupted a total of 38 BEC attacks across 27 organizations &#8211; clearly showcasing the eff...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illumio for Azure Firewall - Combines Benefits of Zero Trust Segmentation and Cloud-Native Firewall</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/illumio-for-azure-firewall-combines-benefits-of-zero-trust/ba-p/3762789</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:57:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/illumio-for-azure-firewall-combines-benefits-of-zero-trust/ba-p/3762789</guid>
      <description>Written by Henry Yan (Sr. Product Marketing Manager)
&#160;
Illumio for Azure Firewall enables organizations to understand application traffic and dependencies and apply consistent protection across environments - limiting exposure, containing breaches, and improving efficiency.
&#160;
Cloud environments are dynamic in nature with applications commonly deployed as code and continuously scaling up and down. This makes it more challenging for organizations to secure their applications and gain visibility into application traffic. Organizations need a holistic view of their environment and granular control...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic disruption of Ransomware and BEC attacks with Microsoft 365 Defender</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/automatic-disruption-of-ransomware-and-bec-attacks-with/ba-p/3738294</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 14:04:30 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/automatic-disruption-of-ransomware-and-bec-attacks-with/ba-p/3738294</guid>
      <description>The ever-growing volume of advanced cybersecurity attacks challenges even the most advanced Security Operations (SOC) teams. Image 1 shows a timeline of a typical human-operated ransomware attack where the attacker encrypted hundreds of devices in just minutes. It demonstrates how quickly threat actors spread and execute attacks and highlights the criticality to quickly identify and contain high-impact attacks to limit the impact to organizations.
&#160;
To help SOC teams address these challenges, we announced automatic attack disruption in Microsoft 365 Defender last year at Microsoft Ignite. This...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automate your alert response actions in Microsoft 365 Defender</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/automate-your-alert-response-actions-in-microsoft-365-defender/ba-p/3732052</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 13:13:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/automate-your-alert-response-actions-in-microsoft-365-defender/ba-p/3732052</guid>
      <description>&#160;
While Microsoft&#8217;s Extended Detection and Response (XDR) solution helps prioritize response activities and provides a unified experience that allows for more effective investigation at the incident level, the increasing volume and speed of sophisticated attacks, still challenges the capacity of most security teams.
&#160;
Automation is growing in importance to close the gap to the speed needed to respond to more attacks faster. Automating the response actions to common alerts in can help you stay ahead of threats, protect your organization more effectively, significantly reduce response times, and...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring Storage Replication - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/monitoring-storage-replication-part-2/ba-p/3762073</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/monitoring-storage-replication-part-2/ba-p/3762073</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Hi folks! My name is Felipe Binotto, Cloud Solution Architect, based in Australia.
&#160;
This is part 2 of Monitoring Storage Replication, if you missed part 1 you can find it HERE.
&#160;
In part 1, we configured an Automation Runbook to collect replication data for Storage Accounts and stored it in a custom table in a Log Analytics workspace.
&#160;
In this post, I will demonstrate how you can leverage that data stored in Log Analytics to generate Azure Alerts which trigger a Logic App and send a customized email to the owner of the Storage Account which is defined as a tag value of the Stora...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prioritize Risk remediation with Microsoft Defender for Cloud Attack Path Analysis</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/prioritize-risk-remediation-with-microsoft-defender-for-cloud/ba-p/3761155</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 13:59:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/prioritize-risk-remediation-with-microsoft-defender-for-cloud/ba-p/3761155</guid>
      <description>&#160;
Introduction&#160;
Our previous blogs &#8220;A Proactive Approach to Cloud Security Posture Management with Microsoft Defender for Cloud,&#8221; and &#8220;Proacting Hunting with Cloud Security Explorer in Defender for Cloud - Microsoft Community Hub&#8221; emphasized the importance of proactive security posture management and outlined a successful organizational structure for security teams.&#8239; As a follow up article here we walk you through the scenarios how to identify and mitigate the biggest security risk issues while distinguishing them from less risky issues.&#160;
&#160;
Cloud environments are dynamically changing and to su...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Remote Help and Supporting Users with Intune</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/enabling-remote-help-and-supporting-users-with-intune/ba-p/3754586</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/enabling-remote-help-and-supporting-users-with-intune/ba-p/3754586</guid>
      <description>Enabling Remote Help on Tenant
Remote help for Intune is a premium add-on that is licensed separately. So, first step in enabling Remote help is either purchasing its license for the end users or having a trial for Remote help feature. Once you have licenses available, it would be possible to enable Remote help for tenant.
&#160;
Snippet from Tenant Administration - Remote Help View
&#160;
&#160;
Enabling Remote help can be done on Intune console &#8211; Tenant Admin Node &#8211; Remote Help view. As you can see in the snippet, it is disabled by default. Configurable With a click on &#8220;Configure&#8221; button.
&#160;
Configure Remot...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Push ASR rules with Security Settings Management on Microsoft Defender for Endpoint managed devices</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/push-asr-rules-with-security-settings-management-on-microsoft/ba-p/3635129</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 23:43:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/push-asr-rules-with-security-settings-management-on-microsoft/ba-p/3635129</guid>
      <description>In May 2022, we announced the general availability of Security Settings Management for Microsoft Defender for Endpoint. This release empowered security teams to configure devices with their desired antivirus, EDR and firewall settings without needing to deploy and implement additional tools or infrastructure.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
As we continue our momentum around Security Settings Management, we are excited to announce that we are expanding this capability to help cover more scenarios with support for Attack Surface Reduction (ASR) rules, now in public preview. This release will allow all Defender for Endpoin...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure WAF Notebook for Microsoft Sentinel</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-waf-notebook-for-microsoft-sentinel/ba-p/3754254</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 22:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-waf-notebook-for-microsoft-sentinel/ba-p/3754254</guid>
      <description>Azure Web Application Firewall&#160;(Azure WAF)&#160;detects SQLI attacks and applies block mitigations&#160;by default. In certain instances, this could be a false positive that requires investigation and creation of Azure WAF&#160;exclusions.&#160;In order to complete a successful investigation,&#160;full context about the attack is needed&#160;and a process that guides you through the investigation is required.&#160;Such a&#160;guided&#160;investigation process is automated in this Microsoft Sentinel Notebook and&#160;allows you to tune&#160;Azure&#160;WAF policy with&#160;minimal user interaction.
This&#160;Notebook analyzes&#160;SQL injection attacks on&#160;Azure WAF int...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Defender for Containers to simplify policy management in your Kubernetes Clusters</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/leveraging-defender-for-containers-to-simplify-policy-management/ba-p/3755757</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/leveraging-defender-for-containers-to-simplify-policy-management/ba-p/3755757</guid>
      <description>Introduction
A key part of Kubernetes security includes making sure the cluster is configured to industry and company best practices. This entails controlling what users can do on the cluster and blocking actions that don&#8217;t comply with pre-defined best practices.
&#160;
Out of the box, Kubernetes does not provide a mechanism to write and deploy fine grained policies required per your security and compliance mandates. As a result, you will probably leverage something like Gatekeeper along with Open Policy Agent (OPA).
&#160;
Defender for Containers protects your Kubernetes clusters by continuously assess...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborate securely across organizational boundaries and Microsoft clouds</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/collaborate-securely-across-organizational-boundaries-and/ba-p/3094109</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:31:37 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/collaborate-securely-across-organizational-boundaries-and/ba-p/3094109</guid>
      <description>Hello friends,&#160;
&#160;
Today I&#8217;m super excited to announce that the capability to collaborate across Microsoft clouds is generally available! This means there&#8217;s now support for Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) B2B collaboration across the following Microsoft clouds:
&#160;

Azure Commercial and Azure Government clouds&#160;
Azure Commercial and Azure China clouds (operated by 21Vianet)

Many of you are already using Azure AD, part of Microsoft Entra, to collaborate with external users like suppliers, partners, and vendors within a Microsoft cloud. We heard you also need to share and collaborate with organiz...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
