<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 17:07:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering SOC Analysts: Investigating Identity Threats with Microsoft Defender XDR</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/empowering-soc-analysts-investigating-identity-threats-with/ba-p/4398225</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 17:00:07 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/empowering-soc-analysts-investigating-identity-threats-with/ba-p/4398225</guid>
      <description>Identities have been a top threat vector forever. However, the rise of cloud identity attacks and an ever increasingly complex digital estate has made a tough problem even harder. Securing identities has always required a close partnership between two different functional teams &#8211; the identity and access management teams that are responsible for managing, authenticating, and authorizing user access to protected systems and data; and the security teams that detect and respond to threats across the entire digital estate.&#160;&#160;
Nowhere is this more apparent than during a security incident. Let&#8217;s take ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Purview pricing options for protecting AI apps and agents</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/new-purview-pricing-options-for-protecting-ai-apps-and-agents/ba-p/4408151</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/new-purview-pricing-options-for-protecting-ai-apps-and-agents/ba-p/4408151</guid>
      <description>AI innovation is impacting every industry, business process, and individual. About 75% of knowledge workers today are currently using some sort of AI in their day to day [Work Trends Index] At the same time, the regulatory landscape is evolving at an unprecedented pace. Around the world, at least 69 countries have proposed more than 1,000 AI-related policy initiatives and legal frameworks to address public concerns around AI safety and governance [AI Regulations Around the World 2025]. Microsoft Purview offers integrated data security, governance, and compliance solutions for the era of AI&#8212;hel...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
