<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:10:17 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Connect with us at the Gartner Security &amp; Risk Management Summit</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/connect-with-us-at-the-gartner-security-risk-management-summit/ba-p/4420744</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/connect-with-us-at-the-gartner-security-risk-management-summit/ba-p/4420744</guid>
      <description>Security professionals visiting booths scattered around a hall, eager for solutions to today&#8217;s top cybersecurity challenges to protect their resources and people. The hum of hundreds of conversations. Presenters in packed sessions sharing expertise, trends, and stories to energize attendees. Few occasions are as thrilling as a cybersecurity event, knowing that all around you are people who understand the frustrating challenges and exciting wins of working in cybersecurity. The rise in quantum computing and AI as tools used by adversaries make such events both inspiring and necessary as profess...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Mitigating Golden SAML Attacks</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/understanding-and-mitigating-golden-saml-attacks/ba-p/4418864</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/understanding-and-mitigating-golden-saml-attacks/ba-p/4418864</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third in our series of articles on dealing with advanced identity-related attacks. This time, we&#8217;ll discuss Golden Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) attacks.
Password attacks (e.g., password spray, breach replay, and phishing) are responsible for compromising millions of accounts each month. Every second, Microsoft detects and blocks more than 7,000 password attacks. In contrast, Golden SAML attacks are rare. At the time of this writing, the customer-facing cybersecurity response teams at Microsoft have reported 20 Golden SAML attacks on fewer than ten unique customers o...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
