<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:08:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>New Identity Secure Score recommendations in General Availability</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/new-identity-secure-score-recommendations-in-general/ba-p/4369133</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/new-identity-secure-score-recommendations-in-general/ba-p/4369133</guid>
      <description>Last year, we emphasized our investments in Microsoft Entra recommendations within our Transparency in Adoption investment area. The primary objective of Microsoft Entra recommendations is to serve as a trusted advisor for enhancing security posture and improving employee productivity. Furthermore, it aims to provide actionable insights based on best practices and industry standards to assist in securing your organization.&#160;
Since the launch of Microsoft Entra recommendations and the announcement of various recommendation releases, we would like to highlight that 11 new Identity Secure Score re...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the new Defender for Identity sensor management API</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/introducing-the-new-defender-for-identity-sensor-management-api/ba-p/4367164</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:25:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/introducing-the-new-defender-for-identity-sensor-management-api/ba-p/4367164</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Defender for Identity is a cloud-based security solution that helps monitor and protect identities and infrastructure across your organization. Defender for Identity is a core component of Microsoft Defender XDR, leveraging signals from both on-premises Active Directory and cloud identities to help you better identify, detect, and investigate advanced cyberthreats directed at your organization.
Last year Microsoft Defender for Identity&#160;introduced a Graph based API to view Defender for Identity Health issues. Today I am going to discuss the new Defender for Identity sensor management ...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
