<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:07:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>&#8203;&#8203;Investigating Industrial Control Systems using Microsoft&#8217;s ICSpector open-source framework</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/investigating-industrial-control-systems-using-microsoft-s/ba-p/4120580</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/investigating-industrial-control-systems-using-microsoft-s/ba-p/4120580</guid>
      <description>Industrial Control Systems (ICS) security has been a subject of research for many years, spurred, in part, by recent state-sponsored ICS-targeting malware and supply-chain attacks like the ZPMC cranes spying concerns that threaten critical infrastructure. Given the potential harm to thousands of people if water treatment facilities, power plants and nuclear reactors or other systems are breached, the stakes are high. Unfortunately, forensics for ICS devices is not as advanced as in IT environments like Windows and Linux. This can stall forensics investigation when incidents occur.&#160;
&#160;
To overco...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborate across M365 tenants with Entra ID multi-tenant organization</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/collaborate-across-m365-tenants-with-entra-id-multi-tenant/ba-p/4120309</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/collaborate-across-m365-tenants-with-entra-id-multi-tenant/ba-p/4120309</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone,&#160;
&#160;
I&#8217;m excited to announce the general availability of Microsoft Entra ID multi-tenant organization platform capabilities!&#160;
&#160;
As your organization evolves, you may need to integrate multiple tenants to facilitate collaboration; for example, your organization may have recently acquired a new company, merged with another company, or restructured with newly formed business units. With disparate identity management systems, it can be costly and complex for admins to manage multiple tenants while ensuring users across tenants have access to resources to collaborate.&#160;
&#160;
To enable applic...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
