<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:00:56 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Emphasizing Security by Default with Advanced Microsoft Authenticator Features.</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/emphasizing-security-by-default-with-advanced-microsoft/ba-p/3773130</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/emphasizing-security-by-default-with-advanced-microsoft/ba-p/3773130</guid>
      <description>We&#8216;ve repeatedly emphasized the importance of multifactor authentication (MFA) and emphasized that not all MFA is equal &#8211; the Authenticator is much more secure than phone authentication (so hang up!). Through the implementation of number matching, we've successfully thwarted criminals engaging in MFA fatigue attacks.&#160;
&#160;
While this has been very effective, attackers attempting these methods can still annoy users, and Authenticator prompts&#8212;while extremely helpful when a user is trying to log in&#8212;can provide a &#8220;hook&#8221; for social phishing when triggered by a hacker. In response to this, we took addi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Service Delivery Manager Profile: Sachin Kumar</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/service-delivery-manager-profile-sachin-kumar/ba-p/3973959</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 16:06:42 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/service-delivery-manager-profile-sachin-kumar/ba-p/3973959</guid>
      <description>&#160;

&#160;



&#160;
Service Delivery Manager Profile: Sachin Kumar
Defender Experts for XDR

&#160;

&#160;
"As an SDM, I am committed to walking this path of security alongside our Defender Experts for XDR customers."
-Sachin Kumar, Product Manager

&#160;

&#160;
In the realm of cybersecurity, where digital threats are ever evolving, there are dedicated professionals like Sachin Kumar, who steer organizations towards a more secure future. Sachin is a Service Delivery Manager (SDM) on the Microsoft Defender Experts for XDR service. With a mission to not only mitigate cyberthreats but also foresee them, he plays a vital ro...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
