<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:01:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hunting with Microsoft Graph activity logs</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/hunting-with-microsoft-graph-activity-logs/ba-p/4234632</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/hunting-with-microsoft-graph-activity-logs/ba-p/4234632</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Microsoft Graph is a unified REST API endpoint that allows you to query data from various sources, including data stored in Microsoft 365. Microsoft Graph provides access to a suite of services including Microsoft 365, Enterprise Mobility + Security, and Windows. In the wrong hands, access to Microsoft Graph API can be misused by threat actors to compromise users; for example, by reading emails or files on SharePoint.
&#160;
Responding to and detecting these cloud-based attacks is of utmost priority. Multiple products and logs are available to help with threat investigation and detecti...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security Exposure Management Graph: Prioritization is the king</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-security-exposure-management-graph-prioritization-is/ba-p/4160316</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:37:43 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/microsoft-security-exposure-management-graph-prioritization-is/ba-p/4160316</guid>
      <description>Recap: Microsoft&#8217;s Security Exposure Management Graph
In the dynamic world of cybersecurity, staying ahead of threats is not merely about reacting to threats but proactively understanding and&#160;managing the security posture of every asset within an organization. The introduction of Microsoft&#8217;s ExposureGraphEdges &amp; ExposureGraphNodes tables within Advanced Hunting signifies a substantial advancement in exposure management tools. These tables&#160;encapsulate the entire dataset of the Microsoft Security Exposure Management Graph. In this blog, we delve into key concepts and&#160;provide powerful queries tha...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
