<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:10:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Microsoft M365 Copilot and AI with Microsoft's Suite of Security Products - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/securing-microsoft-m365-copilot-and-ai-with-microsoft-s-suite-of/ba-p/4410425</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-blog/securing-microsoft-m365-copilot-and-ai-with-microsoft-s-suite-of/ba-p/4410425</guid>
      <description>Microsoft 365 Copilot and AI applications created in Azure AI Foundry are transforming productivity, but they also introduce new security challenges for businesses. Organizations embracing these AI capabilities must guard against risks such as data leaks, novel AI-driven threats (e.g. prompt injection attacks), and compliance violations. Microsoft offers a comprehensive suite of products to help secure and govern AI solutions. This multipart guide provides a detailed roadmap for using Microsoft&#8217;s security services together to protect AI deployments and Copilot integrations in an enterprise env...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhance identity security and resilience to minimize operational disruptions</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/enhance-identity-security-and-resilience-to-minimize-operational/ba-p/4411258</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/enhance-identity-security-and-resilience-to-minimize-operational/ba-p/4411258</guid>
      <description>The rapid advancements in technology are reshaping the way organizations, including banks, insurers, investment firms, and other global financial services industry (FSI) firms secure their businesses. Strong operational resilience and the ability to recover quickly from disruption or cyberattack is more critical than ever as infrastructure is required to respond to a complex and dynamic risk environment coupled with an evolving regulatory landscape.
The financial services sector is experiencing increased regulatory oversight aimed at enhancing its stability, security, and resilience. On Januar...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
