<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 16:01:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learn the steps needed to protect your data and manage identity</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/learn-the-steps-needed-to-protect-your-data-and-manage-identity/ba-p/3909959</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/learn-the-steps-needed-to-protect-your-data-and-manage-identity/ba-p/3909959</guid>
      <description>Today we&#8217;re sharing some new training resources and opportunities to help you build skills with these solutions&#8212;so you can use them now or get ready for a Microsoft certification exam.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
Help your organization secure your data estate with the new Microsoft Purview training guide.&#160;
Microsoft Purview plays an integral part in securing your organization's data across clouds, devices, and platforms.&#160;
&#160;
The&#160;Microsoft training guide for Purview and data protection is an easy-to-navigate&#160;guide that quickly walks you through business needs related to information protection, insider risk management (...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming Soon &#8211; Platform SSO for macOS</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/coming-soon-platform-sso-for-macos/ba-p/3902280</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/coming-soon-platform-sso-for-macos/ba-p/3902280</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year we took a big step towards improving customers&#8217; experience with Apple devices by providing companies with the Microsoft Enterprise SSO plug-in for Apple devices. This plug-in enables&#160;Microsoft Entra ID users to have device-wide single sign-on (SSO) for all apps and websites in a consistent, secure, and seamless way. Best of all, it always stays up to date with the latest Microsoft technologies as they evolve.&#160;
&#160;
Today we're announcing a powerful enhancement to these capabilities - Platform SSO for macOS. This enhancement is designed to make using your macOS devices more seaml...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
