<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:06:28 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trusted Signing is in Public Preview</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/trusted-signing-is-in-public-preview/ba-p/4103457</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/trusted-signing-is-in-public-preview/ba-p/4103457</guid>
      <description>Trusted Signing has launched into Public Preview! The Trusted Signing service (formerly Azure Code Signing) is a Microsoft fully managed end-to-end signing solution for developers.&#160;&#160;
&#160;
What is the Trusted Signing service?&#160;
Trusted Signing is a complete code signing service with an intuitive experience for developers and IT professionals, backed by a Microsoft managed certification authority. The service supports both public and private trust signing scenarios and includes a timestamping service. With Trusted Signing, users enjoy a productive, performant, and delightful experience on Windows wi...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling AKS egress using an HTTP Proxy</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/controlling-aks-egress-using-an-http-proxy/ba-p/4119407</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/controlling-aks-egress-using-an-http-proxy/ba-p/4119407</guid>
      <description>Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) clusters, whether deployed into a managed or custom virtual network, have certain outbound dependencies necessary to function properly. Previously, in environments requiring internet access to be routed through HTTP proxies, this was a problem. Nodes had no way of bootstrapping the configuration, environment variables, and certificates necessary to access internet services.
This feature adds HTTP proxy support to AKS clusters, exposing a straightforward interface that cluster operators can use to secure AKS-required network traffic in proxy-dependent environments...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
