<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 16:01:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GA: System-preferred multifactor authentication</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/ga-system-preferred-multifactor-authentication/ba-p/3773138</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/ga-system-preferred-multifactor-authentication/ba-p/3773138</guid>
      <description>In previous blogs, we've emphasized the importance of multifactor authentication (MFA). Today, organizations and end users are using various authentication methods, providing varying levels of security.&#160;Users often choose less secure MFA methods, despite having access to more secure options due to a range of factors such as convenience, lack of awareness, or technical limitations.
&#160;
To encourage users to authenticate with the strongest method available to them, we&#8217;re announcing system-preferred authentication for MFA.&#160;This system prompts the user to sign in with the most secure method they&#8217;ve ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designs for Accomplishing Microsoft Sentinel Scalable Ingestion</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/designs-for-accomplishing-microsoft-sentinel-scalable-ingestion/ba-p/3741516</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:51:14 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/designs-for-accomplishing-microsoft-sentinel-scalable-ingestion/ba-p/3741516</guid>
      <description>**Thank you to the Microsoft Sentinel CxE team, Jeff Wolford, and&#160;@Preeti_Krishna&#160;for the assistance with this document.**
&#160;
This blog will provide a high-level overview of potential architecture designs that can be used to achieve a high availability, scalable ingestion pipeline.&#160;The main components that will be covered in the designs will be:&#160;

Load Balancer&#160;
Forwarder Systems&#160;
Data Sources (Coming from endpoints)&#160;

The architectures can be categorized into 3 main scenarios:&#160;

Azure based: Components for collection reside within the Azure platform.&#160;
Hybrid: One component resides outside of A...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
