<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:02:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Entra ID Governance Entitlement Management New Generally Available Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/microsoft-entra-id-governance-entitlement-management-new/ba-p/2466929</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-azure-ad-blog/microsoft-entra-id-governance-entitlement-management-new/ba-p/2466929</guid>
      <description>With Microsoft Entra ID Governance, you can effectively manage your organization&#8217;s security and identity governance needs and boost employee productivity by implementing appropriate processes and enhancing visibility. The Microsoft Entra platform empowers you with the ability to guarantee that the right people have the right access to the right resources.&#160;&#160;
We&#8217;re excited to announce the general availability of a set of capabilities in Entitlement Management available through Microsoft Entra ID Governance to help you strengthen your identity governance posture.&#160;
&#160;
1. Extending the access lifecy...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft empowers partners to securely build their own connector on its Open App Connector Platform</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/microsoft-empowers-partners-to-securely-build-their-own/ba-p/3876496</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:46:58 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-defender-blog/microsoft-empowers-partners-to-securely-build-their-own/ba-p/3876496</guid>
      <description>In today's rapidly evolving business landscape, the adoption of Software as a Service (SaaS) applications has skyrocketed, enabling organizations to streamline operations and enhance productivity. However, with the growing number of SaaS applications, ensuring robust security and protecting sensitive data has become a paramount concern. Microsoft recognizes the significance of this challenge and offers a comprehensive solution through our Microsoft Defender suite.
&#160;
At the heart of this solution lie our app connectors, which serve as vital bridges between customers' SaaS apps and Microsoft's p...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitivity label support in Microsoft Fabric and Power BI enables end-to-end information protection</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/sensitivity-label-support-in-microsoft-fabric-and-power-bi/ba-p/3874178</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/sensitivity-label-support-in-microsoft-fabric-and-power-bi/ba-p/3874178</guid>
      <description>Did you know that 88% of organizations lack the confidence to prevent sensitive data loss?1&#160;Discovery and classification of sensitive data is important for organizations who want to better protect sensitive personally identifiable information (PII) and corporate intellectual property. When these sensitive labeled files are used in business intelligence and analytics solutions, it&#8217;s important they remain protected and are shared and accessed only by authorized individuals.
&#160;
With Microsoft Purview Information Protection, we provide a built-in, intelligent, unified, and extensible solution to pr...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
