<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 17:06:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Network Security @ RSA Conference 2023 (April 23-27)</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-network-security-rsa-conference-2023-april-23-27/ba-p/3800541</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 16:48:27 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/azure-network-security-rsa-conference-2023-april-23-27/ba-p/3800541</guid>
      <description>
&#160;
We&#8217;re thrilled to participate and connect with you at RSA Conference 2023 (RSAC) in San Francisco from April 23-27, 2023. Visit us throughout the week at the Microsoft booth at Moscone North Expo to engage with Microsoft product experts, experience interactive demos on network security technologies, and attend our in-booth theater sessions.
&#160;
Azure Network Security @ Microsoft Booth
Join us at the Microsoft booth for our 2 theater sessions focused on Azure Network Security:
&#160;
Secure your network infrastructure with Zero Trust, cloud-native network security | Thursday, April 27th, 10:40AM - ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Monitor: Logs Ingestion API Tips &amp; Tricks</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-monitor-logs-ingestion-api-tips-amp-tricks/ba-p/3792081</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 15:27:39 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/azure-monitor-logs-ingestion-api-tips-amp-tricks/ba-p/3792081</guid>
      <description>Hello followers and welcome back to this new post of mine 
&#160;
Today I am going to share with you an interesting experience in configuring the Logs ingestion using the new API in Azure Monitor in a data collection rule created using ARM templates.
&#160;
In my previous HTTP Data Collector API in a real customer scenario post, I showed a possible use of the old HTTP Data Collector API but since things changed a lot with the release of the Azure Monitor Agent I decided to give the new Logs Ingestion API a try.
&#160;
I basically followed the Tutorial: Send data to Azure Monitor Logs using REST API (Resource...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
