<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 22:13:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <item><title>Monthly news -  February 2026</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/monthly-news-february-2026/ba-p/4491826</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:36:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/monthly-news-february-2026/ba-p/4491826</guid><description>Microsoft DefenderMonthly news - February 2026 Edition
This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month across our Defender products. In this edition, we are looking at all the goodness from January 2026. Defender for Cloud has its own Monthly News post, have a look here.&#160;
&#128640; New Virtual Ninja Show episode:

Discovering Microsoft Sentinel MCP server
Microsoft Sentinel for SAP: What's New, What's Gone, and What's Next
Unlocking Security Context with Microsoft Sentinel Graph
Inside OAuth App: Risks, Real Attacks, and Ho...</description></item><item><title>Cloud forensics: Forensic readiness and incident response in Azure Virtual Desktop</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/cloud-forensics-forensic-readiness-and-incident-response-in/ba-p/4488274</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/cloud-forensics-forensic-readiness-and-incident-response-in/ba-p/4488274</guid><description>Co-authors: Dan Weinstock and Christoph Dreymann
Azure Virtual Desktop (AVD) has rapidly become a core tool for enabling remote work at scale. Consequently, it&#8217;s also emerging as a target for threat actors. Recent Microsoft Incident Response engagements show that threat actors are exploiting AVD deployments for lateral movement and persistence. By hijacking legitimate AVD user accounts, they gain what is essentially a trusted &#8220;endpoint&#8221; inside the network without having to install malware.
Why does this matter to incident responders?
AVD intrusions can be stealthy and fast-moving, and responde...</description></item><item><title>Extending Defender&#8217;s AI Threat Protection to Microsoft Foundry Agents</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/extending-defender-s-ai-threat-protection-to-microsoft-foundry/ba-p/4491927</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/extending-defender-s-ai-threat-protection-to-microsoft-foundry/ba-p/4491927</guid><description>AI is moving from responses to actions
In our previous announcement, we introduced new threat protection capabilities for custom AI applications, helping organizations detect prompt injections, jailbreak attempts, sensitive data exposure, and other AI-specific risks.
But the AI landscape is evolving rapidly.
AI systems are no longer limited to single-turn prompts and responses. Modern applications increasingly rely on AI agents &#8211; autonomous, multi-step systems that can reason, plan, call tools, access data sources, and take actions on behalf of users. While this unlocks powerful new scenarios,...</description></item><item><title>The Agentic SOC Era: How Sentinel MCP Enables Autonomous Security Reasoning</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-agentic-soc-era-how-sentinel-mcp-enables-autonomous-security/ba-p/4491003</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:09:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-agentic-soc-era-how-sentinel-mcp-enables-autonomous-security/ba-p/4491003</guid><description>Security teams already have access to enormous volumes of telemetry across identity, endpoint, network, and cloud. The real challenge isn&#8217;t collecting more data. It&#8217;s turning that data into faster decisions and better protection. This is where AI changes the game.&#160;&#160;
Microsoft Sentinel MCP Server, now generally available,&#160;augments&#160;analysts with intelligence that can reason across signals, automate investigations, and surface what truly matters.&#160;AI helps&#160;Security&#160;Operations Center (SOCs)&#160;move faster, reduce fatigue, and measurably improve the security posture of the organization.&#160;
The Problem: D...</description></item><item><title>The Microsoft Copilot Data Connector for Microsoft Sentinel is Now in Public Preview</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-microsoft-copilot-data-connector-for-microsoft-sentinel-is/ba-p/4491986</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:42:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-microsoft-copilot-data-connector-for-microsoft-sentinel-is/ba-p/4491986</guid><description>We are happy to announce a new data connector that is available to the public: the Microsoft Copilot data connector for Microsoft Sentinel. The new Microsoft Copilot data connector will allow for audit logs and activities generated by different offerings of Copilot to be ingested into Microsoft Sentinel and Microsoft Sentinel data lake. This allows for Copilot activities to be leveraged within Microsoft Sentinel features such as analytic rules/custom detections, Workbooks, automation, and more. This also allows for Copilot data to be sent to Sentinel data lake, which opens the possibilities fo...</description></item><item><title>Zero Trust with Azure Firewall, Azure DDoS Protection and Azure WAF: A practical use case</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/zero-trust-with-azure-firewall-azure-ddos-protection-and-azure/ba-p/4490595</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:47:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/zero-trust-with-azure-firewall-azure-ddos-protection-and-azure/ba-p/4490595</guid><description>Introduction
Zero Trust has emerged as the defining security ethos of the modern enterprise. It is guided by a simple but powerful principle: &#8220;Never trust, always verify.&#8221; This principle is more relevant now than ever as cyberattacks continue to trend upward in both frequency and impact, affecting organizations of every size and industry. No entity large or small can assume immunity. As a result, adopting Zero Trust is no longer optional, it is a foundational requirement for designing secure, resilient architectures.
A key tenet of Zero Trust is the assumption of breach, thus designing systems...</description></item><item><title>Building Secure, Enterprise Ready AI Agents with Purview SDK and Agent Framework</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/building-secure-enterprise-ready-ai-agents-with-purview-sdk-and/ba-p/4492356</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:32:33 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/building-secure-enterprise-ready-ai-agents-with-purview-sdk-and/ba-p/4492356</guid><description>&#160;
At Microsoft Ignite, we announced the public preview of Purview integration with the Agent Framework SDK&#8212;making it easier to build AI agents that are secure, compliant, and enterprise&#8209;ready from day one.
AI agents are quickly moving from demos to production. They reason over enterprise data, collaborate with other agents, and take real actions. As that happens, one thing becomes non&#8209;negotiable:
Governance has to be built in. That&#8217;s where Purview SDK comes in.
Agentic AI Changes the Security Model
Traditional apps expose risks at the UI or API layer.AI agents are different.
Agents can:

Proce...</description></item><item><title>General Availability of Microsoft Purview eDiscovery Graph API for E3 Customers</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/general-availability-of-microsoft-purview-ediscovery-graph-api/ba-p/4489678</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:52:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/general-availability-of-microsoft-purview-ediscovery-graph-api/ba-p/4489678</guid><description>As of December 1st, 2025, the Microsoft Purview eDiscovery Graph API Standard hit General Availability (GA). It provides a programmatic way to manage eDiscovery cases, searches, holds, and exports for organizations that have only M365 E3 licenses. It extends automation capabilities that were previously exclusive to eDiscovery Premium customers with M365 E5 (or equivalent add-on SKU) licenses.
With the eDiscovery Graph APIs, organisations can realise efficiency savings by automating the following elements of their eDiscovery workflow:

Case management &#8211; create new cases, list or get case detail...</description></item></channel>
</rss>
