<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:10:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Streamline user management across Microsoft clouds</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/streamline-user-management-across-microsoft-clouds/ba-p/4422536</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/streamline-user-management-across-microsoft-clouds/ba-p/4422536</guid>
      <description>Government agencies and multinational corporations rely on Microsoft&#8217;s commercial and sovereign clouds, such as the&#160;US Government, China,&#160;and others,&#160;to meet their productivity and collaboration needs, while adhering to data sovereignty and cybersecurity requirements. Since the launch of support for collaboration across Microsoft Clouds, thousands of customers have successfully enabled application access, managed Azure&#160;resources, and used SharePoint across different Microsoft clouds.&#160;
To further support these scenarios, we&#8217;re excited to announce that cross-tenant synchronization support across...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Named a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for CNAPP: Key Takeaways for Security Buyers</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-named-a-leader-in-the-idc-marketscape-for-cnapp-key/ba-p/4427071</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 15:54:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/microsoft-named-a-leader-in-the-idc-marketscape-for-cnapp-key/ba-p/4427071</guid>
      <description>&#160;
The cloud-native application protection platform (CNAPP) market continues to evolve rapidly as organizations look to secure increasingly complex cloud environments. In the recently published IDC MarketScape: Worldwide CNAPP 2025 Vendor Assessment, Microsoft has been recognized as a Leader. We believe this recognition reaffirms Microsoft&#8217;s commitment to delivering comprehensive, AI-powered, and integrated security solutions for multicloud environments.
&#160;

&#160;
IDC MarketScape vendor analysis model is designed to provide an overview of the competitive fitness of technology and suppliers in a give...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
