<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:13:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud forensics: Why enabling Microsoft Azure Key Vaults matters</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/cloud-forensics-why-enabling-microsoft-azure-key-vaults-matters/ba-p/4432149</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:36:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/cloud-forensics-why-enabling-microsoft-azure-key-vaults-matters/ba-p/4432149</guid>
      <description>Co-authors - Christoph Dreymann&#160; -&#160; Abul Azed&#160; -&#160; Shiva P.
Introduction
As organizations increase their cloud adoption to accelerate AI readiness, Microsoft Incident Response has observed the rise of cloud-based threats as attackers seek to access sensitive data and exploit vulnerabilities stemming from misconfigurations often caused by rapid deployments. In this blog series, Cloud Forensics, we share insights from our frontline investigations to help organizations better understand the evolving threat landscape and implement effective strategies to protect their cloud environments.
This blog ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fishing for Syslog with Azure Kubernetes and Logstash</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/fishing-for-syslog-with-azure-kubernetes-and-logstash/ba-p/4431809</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 17:27:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/fishing-for-syslog-with-azure-kubernetes-and-logstash/ba-p/4431809</guid>
      <description>Deploy Secure Syslog Collection on Azure Kubernetes Service with Terraform
Organizations managing distributed infrastructure face a common challenge: collecting syslog data securely and reliably from various sources. Whether you're aggregating logs from network devices, Linux servers, or applications, you need a solution that scales with your environment while maintaining security standards.
This post walks through deploying Logstash on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) to collect RFC 5425 syslog messages over TLS. The solution uses Terraform for infrastructure automation and forwards collected l...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
