<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:14:38 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How-To Use Graph Object Change Notifications</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/how-to-use-graph-object-change-notifications/ba-p/4403939</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:12:10 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/how-to-use-graph-object-change-notifications/ba-p/4403939</guid>
      <description>Hi, Jonas and Roland here!
Or as we say in the north of Germany: "Moin Moin!"
We recently worked on a mechanism to sync Entra ID group memberships into an Azure SQL table and would like to share our learnings.
This article is part of a series of articles about Entra ID group membership synchronization. Check them out here: https://aka.ms/JonasOhmsenBlogs
Introduction
In this article we will dive deeper into &#8220;Option #4: Delta Notification&#8221; as described in our previous article: How-To Sync EntraID Group Memberships Into Any System
TL/DR
In short, we&#8217;ve built an Azure Function app to synchronize ...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archiving Selective Microsoft Defender Logs to Azure Data Explorer</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/archiving-selective-microsoft-defender-logs-to-azure-data/ba-p/4398227</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-endpoint/archiving-selective-microsoft-defender-logs-to-azure-data/ba-p/4398227</guid>
      <description>This blog builds upon the insightful Microsoft Community Hub article by Jeff Chin, Archive MDE Data to Event Hubs to ADX | Microsoft Community Hub.
While the original guide thoroughly explains the process of forwarding Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE) data into Azure Data Explorer (ADX) using Event Hubs, it overlooks a crucial real-world requirement: filtering and archiving logs from a selective subset of devices.&#160;
In large enterprise environments, the sheer volume of Defender logs can be overwhelming and costly to retain. For instance, imagine an organization with 10,000 onboarded device...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
