<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:07:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Keep your online activity safer on public Wi-Fi with Microsoft Defender for individuals</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/keep-your-online-activity-safer-on-public-wi-fi-with-microsoft/ba-p/4251376</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/security-compliance-and-identity/keep-your-online-activity-safer-on-public-wi-fi-with-microsoft/ba-p/4251376</guid>
      <description>&#160;
Figure 1 - Privacy protection UI on the Defender mobile app
&#160;
Public Wi-Fi is usually free, easy and convenient, but not necessarily always safe. As they say, there is no &#8216;free lunch&#8217; .
&#160;
Microsoft Defender for individuals1 aims to provide a safer online experience wherever you go and late last year, we introduced privacy protection (VPN)2 ,&#160; so you can browse without having to worry about your personal data being intercepted over an unsecure Wi-Fi connection
&#160;
Check out the previous&#160;blog to learn more about the risks of unsecure WiFi and how a Defender VPN increases your online safety
&#160;
Evo...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Driven Guided Response for SOCs with Microsoft Copilot for Security</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/ai-driven-guided-response-for-socs-with-microsoft-copilot-for/ba-p/4257138</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:08:35 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/ai-driven-guided-response-for-socs-with-microsoft-copilot-for/ba-p/4257138</guid>
      <description>In today's evolving cybersecurity landscape, security operation centers (SOCs) are constantly bombarded with incidents ranging from minor alerts to highly complex threats. Given this surge in cyberthreats, security teams are often overwhelmed by the sheer volume of incidents, many of which require time-consuming manual investigation. In response to this challenge, Microsoft&#8217;s Copilot for Security guided response has become a vital tool for enterprise customers. Copilot guided response is a state-of-the-art AI-driven system that helps analysts efficiently navigate incidents by providing real-ti...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
