<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:18:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify your identity landscape, reduce risk, and modernize access for any identity</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/simplify-your-identity-landscape-reduce-risk-and-modernize/ba-p/4486059</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-entra-blog/simplify-your-identity-landscape-reduce-risk-and-modernize/ba-p/4486059</guid>
      <description>Organizations everywhere want easier ways to manage identities, reduce risk, and update access for people, apps, devices, and even agents. In her recent identity priorities blog, Joy Chik shared a clear direction for the future: identity isn&#8217;t only about security&#8212;it&#8217;s becoming the foundation for everything. The path ahead includes uniting identity and network access with an Access Fabric, improving governance, and bringing AI-powered protection and operations to every team. The possibilities have never been greater.
But vision only becomes impact when teams can do something with it.
That&#8217;s why...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run a SQL Query with Azure ARC</title>
      <link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/run-a-sql-query-with-azure-arc/ba-p/4487765</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:49:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/run-a-sql-query-with-azure-arc/ba-p/4487765</guid>
      <description>Hi all,
In this article, you can find a way to retrieve database permission from all your onboarded databases through Azure Arc. This idea is born from a customer request around maintaining a standard permission set, in a very wide environment (about 1000 SQL server).
This solution is based on Azure Arc, so first you need to onboard your SQL server to Azure Arc and enable the SQL server extension. If you want to test Azure Arc in a test environment, you can use the Azure Jumpstart, in this repo you will find ready-to-deploy arm templates the deploy demos environments.
The other solution compon...</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
