<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Aggregator Feed</title>
    <link>https://hitem.github.io/rss-aggregator/aggregated_feed.xml</link>
    <description>An aggregated feed of Microsoft blogs</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 22:10:45 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <item><title>Monthly news -  February 2026</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/monthly-news-february-2026/ba-p/4491826</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:36:55 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/monthly-news-february-2026/ba-p/4491826</guid><description>Microsoft DefenderMonthly news - February 2026 Edition
This is our monthly "What's new" blog post, summarizing product updates and various new assets we released over the past month across our Defender products. In this edition, we are looking at all the goodness from January 2026. Defender for Cloud has its own Monthly News post, have a look here.&#160;
&#128640; New Virtual Ninja Show episode:

Discovering Microsoft Sentinel MCP server
Microsoft Sentinel for SAP: What's New, What's Gone, and What's Next
Unlocking Security Context with Microsoft Sentinel Graph
Inside OAuth App: Risks, Real Attacks, and Ho...</description></item><item><title>Cloud forensics: Forensic readiness and incident response in Azure Virtual Desktop</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/cloud-forensics-forensic-readiness-and-incident-response-in/ba-p/4488274</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-experts-blog/cloud-forensics-forensic-readiness-and-incident-response-in/ba-p/4488274</guid><description>Co-authors: Dan Weinstock and Christoph Dreymann
Azure Virtual Desktop (AVD) has rapidly become a core tool for enabling remote work at scale. Consequently, it&#8217;s also emerging as a target for threat actors. Recent Microsoft Incident Response engagements show that threat actors are exploiting AVD deployments for lateral movement and persistence. By hijacking legitimate AVD user accounts, they gain what is essentially a trusted &#8220;endpoint&#8221; inside the network without having to install malware.
Why does this matter to incident responders?
AVD intrusions can be stealthy and fast-moving, and responde...</description></item><item><title>Extending Defender&#8217;s AI Threat Protection to Microsoft Foundry Agents</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/extending-defender-s-ai-threat-protection-to-microsoft-foundry/ba-p/4491927</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:49:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-for-cloud/extending-defender-s-ai-threat-protection-to-microsoft-foundry/ba-p/4491927</guid><description>AI is moving from responses to actions
In our previous announcement, we introduced new threat protection capabilities for custom AI applications, helping organizations detect prompt injections, jailbreak attempts, sensitive data exposure, and other AI-specific risks.
But the AI landscape is evolving rapidly.
AI systems are no longer limited to single-turn prompts and responses. Modern applications increasingly rely on AI agents &#8211; autonomous, multi-step systems that can reason, plan, call tools, access data sources, and take actions on behalf of users. While this unlocks powerful new scenarios,...</description></item><item><title>The Agentic SOC Era: How Sentinel MCP Enables Autonomous Security Reasoning</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-agentic-soc-era-how-sentinel-mcp-enables-autonomous-security/ba-p/4491003</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 23:09:53 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-agentic-soc-era-how-sentinel-mcp-enables-autonomous-security/ba-p/4491003</guid><description>Security teams already have access to enormous volumes of telemetry across identity, endpoint, network, and cloud. The real challenge isn&#8217;t collecting more data. It&#8217;s turning that data into faster decisions and better protection. This is where AI changes the game.&#160;&#160;
Microsoft Sentinel MCP Server, now generally available,&#160;augments&#160;analysts with intelligence that can reason across signals, automate investigations, and surface what truly matters.&#160;AI helps&#160;Security&#160;Operations Center (SOCs)&#160;move faster, reduce fatigue, and measurably improve the security posture of the organization.&#160;
The Problem: D...</description></item><item><title>The Microsoft Copilot Data Connector for Microsoft Sentinel is Now in Public Preview</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-microsoft-copilot-data-connector-for-microsoft-sentinel-is/ba-p/4491986</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:42:52 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/the-microsoft-copilot-data-connector-for-microsoft-sentinel-is/ba-p/4491986</guid><description>We are happy to announce a new data connector that is available to the public: the Microsoft Copilot data connector for Microsoft Sentinel. The new Microsoft Copilot data connector will allow for audit logs and activities generated by different offerings of Copilot to be ingested into Microsoft Sentinel and Microsoft Sentinel data lake. This allows for Copilot activities to be leveraged within Microsoft Sentinel features such as analytic rules/custom detections, Workbooks, automation, and more. This also allows for Copilot data to be sent to Sentinel data lake, which opens the possibilities fo...</description></item><item><title>Zero Trust with Azure Firewall, Azure DDoS Protection and Azure WAF: A practical use case</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/zero-trust-with-azure-firewall-azure-ddos-protection-and-azure/ba-p/4490595</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:47:23 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/zero-trust-with-azure-firewall-azure-ddos-protection-and-azure/ba-p/4490595</guid><description>Introduction
Zero Trust has emerged as the defining security ethos of the modern enterprise. It is guided by a simple but powerful principle: &#8220;Never trust, always verify.&#8221; This principle is more relevant now than ever as cyberattacks continue to trend upward in both frequency and impact, affecting organizations of every size and industry. No entity large or small can assume immunity. As a result, adopting Zero Trust is no longer optional, it is a foundational requirement for designing secure, resilient architectures.
A key tenet of Zero Trust is the assumption of breach, thus designing systems...</description></item><item><title>Building Secure, Enterprise Ready AI Agents with Purview SDK and Agent Framework</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/building-secure-enterprise-ready-ai-agents-with-purview-sdk-and/ba-p/4492356</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:32:33 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/building-secure-enterprise-ready-ai-agents-with-purview-sdk-and/ba-p/4492356</guid><description>&#160;
At Microsoft Ignite, we announced the public preview of Purview integration with the Agent Framework SDK&#8212;making it easier to build AI agents that are secure, compliant, and enterprise&#8209;ready from day one.
AI agents are quickly moving from demos to production. They reason over enterprise data, collaborate with other agents, and take real actions. As that happens, one thing becomes non&#8209;negotiable:
Governance has to be built in. That&#8217;s where Purview SDK comes in.
Agentic AI Changes the Security Model
Traditional apps expose risks at the UI or API layer.AI agents are different.
Agents can:

Proce...</description></item><item><title>General Availability of Microsoft Purview eDiscovery Graph API for E3 Customers</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/general-availability-of-microsoft-purview-ediscovery-graph-api/ba-p/4489678</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:52:01 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/general-availability-of-microsoft-purview-ediscovery-graph-api/ba-p/4489678</guid><description>As of December 1st, 2025, the Microsoft Purview eDiscovery Graph API Standard hit General Availability (GA). It provides a programmatic way to manage eDiscovery cases, searches, holds, and exports for organizations that have only M365 E3 licenses. It extends automation capabilities that were previously exclusive to eDiscovery Premium customers with M365 E5 (or equivalent add-on SKU) licenses.
With the eDiscovery Graph APIs, organisations can realise efficiency savings by automating the following elements of their eDiscovery workflow:

Case management &#8211; create new cases, list or get case detail...</description></item><item><title>CRL &amp; AIA Publishing Guidance (Practical PKI Part 2)</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/crl-aia-publishing-guidance-practical-pki-part-2/ba-p/4485713</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/crl-aia-publishing-guidance-practical-pki-part-2/ba-p/4485713</guid><description>My name is Ron Arestia, and I am a Security Researcher with Microsoft&#8217;s Detection and Response Team (DART). We respond to customer cybersecurity incidents to assist with containment and recovery from threat actors. In this blog post, we will be covering CRL and AIA publishing guidance with a focus on the Active Directory Certificate Services (ADCS) offline root Certificate Authority (CA). This is part 2 of a series on practical PKI implementation based around my experience with customer interactions working as a Microsoft engineer.
Feel free to catch up on previous blog posts or jump right int...</description></item><item><title>From signal to strategy: Closing attack paths with identity intelligence</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/from-signal-to-strategy-closing-attack-paths-with-identity/ba-p/4491856</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:54:38 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-defender-xdr-blog/from-signal-to-strategy-closing-attack-paths-with-identity/ba-p/4491856</guid><description>Compromised credentials remain one of the most common entry points for attackers. In the first half of 2025 alone, identity-based attacks surged more than 32% and its estimated that 97% of them are password focused. While that scale is overwhelming, it only takes a single exposed account to give an attacker a foothold from which they can move laterally towards the critical assets they are after. At today&#8217;s attack scale, identity signals need to be connected with broader context to stop attacks earlier in the kill chain.
Today we are excited to share more about how Microsoft Defender can help s...</description></item><item><title>Update: Changing the Account Name Entity Mapping in Microsoft Sentinel</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/update-changing-the-account-name-entity-mapping-in-microsoft/ba-p/4489040</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:25:15 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/update-changing-the-account-name-entity-mapping-in-microsoft/ba-p/4489040</guid><description>The upcoming update introduces more consistent and predictable entity data across analytics, incidents, and automation by standardizing how the Account Name property is populated when using UPN&#8209;based mappings in analytic rules. Going forward, Account Name property will consistently contain only the UPN prefix, with new dedicated fields added for the full UPN and UPN suffix.
While this improves consistency and enables more granular automation, customers who rely on specific Account Name values in automation rules or Logic App playbooks may need to take action.
Timeline&#160;

Effective date:&#160;July 1,...</description></item><item><title>Lake-Only Ingestion for Microsoft Defender Advanced Hunting Tables is Now Generally Available</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/lake-only-ingestion-for-microsoft-defender-advanced-hunting/ba-p/4494206</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:21:07 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/lake-only-ingestion-for-microsoft-defender-advanced-hunting/ba-p/4494206</guid><description>Security teams continue to generate unprecedented volumes of high&#8209;fidelity telemetry across endpoints, identities, cloud apps, and email. While this data is essential for detection, investigation, and threat hunting, it also creates new challenges around scale, cost, and long&#8209;term retention.
Today, we&#8217;re excited to announce the general availability (GA) of lake&#8209;only ingestion for Microsoft XDR Advanced Hunting tables into Microsoft Sentinel Data Lake.
With this release, users can now ingest Advanced Hunting data from:

Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE)
Microsoft Defender for Office 365 (MD...</description></item><item><title>What&#8217;s new in Microsoft Sentinel: February 2026</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/what-s-new-in-microsoft-sentinel-february-2026/ba-p/4494218</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/what-s-new-in-microsoft-sentinel-february-2026/ba-p/4494218</guid><description>February brings a set of new innovations to Sentinel that helps you work with security content across your SOC.
This month&#8217;s updates focus on how security teams ingest, manage, and operationalize content, with new connectors, multi-tenant content distribution capabilities, and an enhanced UEBA Essentials solution to surface high&#8209;risk behavior faster across cloud and identity environments. We&#8217;re also introducing new partner-built agentic experiences available through Microsoft Security Store, enabling customers to extend Sentinel with specialized expertise directly inside their existing workflo...</description></item><item><title>Data lake tier Ingestion for Microsoft Defender Advanced Hunting Tables is Now Generally Available</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/data-lake-tier-ingestion-for-microsoft-defender-advanced-hunting/ba-p/4494206</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:40:45 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/data-lake-tier-ingestion-for-microsoft-defender-advanced-hunting/ba-p/4494206</guid><description>Security teams continue to generate unprecedented volumes of high&#8209;fidelity telemetry across endpoints, identities, cloud apps, and email. While this data is essential for detection, investigation, and threat hunting, it also creates new challenges around scale, cost, and long&#8209;term retention.
Today, we&#8217;re excited to announce the general availability (GA) of data lake tier ingestion for Microsoft XDR Advanced Hunting tables into Microsoft Sentinel data lake.
With this release, users can now ingest Advanced Hunting data from:

Microsoft Defender for Endpoint (MDE)
Microsoft Defender for Office 36...</description></item><item><title>General Availability: IP Network Firewalls for Azure Managed HSM</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/general-availability-ip-network-firewalls-for-azure-managed-hsm/ba-p/4493983</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/general-availability-ip-network-firewalls-for-azure-managed-hsm/ba-p/4493983</guid><description>We are excited to announce the General Availability of&#160;IP Firewalls for&#160;Azure Key Vault Managed HSM&#160;in all public regions.&#160;
The feature allows you to authorize a particular service to access your managed HSM through the Managed HSM Firewall by adding its IP address to the Key Vault Managed HSM&#160;firewall&#160;allowlist. This configuration is best for services that use static IP addresses or well-known ranges.&#160;There is a limit of 10 CIDR ranges for this case, and only IPv4 addresses are supported at this time.&#160;
Note that&#160;firewall&#160;rules only apply to data plane operations. Control plane operations are ...</description></item><item><title>Check This Out! (CTO!) Guide (January 2026)</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/check-this-out-cto-guide-january-2026/ba-p/4494595</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:54:34 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/check-this-out-cto-guide-january-2026/ba-p/4494595</guid><description>Member: TysonPaul | Microsoft Community Hub

From classroom to workforce:&#8239;Helping higher ed faculty prepare students for what&#8217;s next
Team Blog: Microsoft Learn
Author: RWortmanMorris
Published: 01/15/2026
Summary: Microsoft is partnering with higher education institutions to prepare students and faculty for an AI-driven workforce. Through tools like AI Skills Navigator, Microsoft Learn for Educators, and the Microsoft Student Ambassadors program, they offer free, flexible training, credentials, and community support to develop practical AI and digital skills. These initiatives help faculty int...</description></item><item><title>Implementing Azure Lighthouse: A Technical Guide for Service Providers and Enterprises</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/implementing-azure-lighthouse-a-technical-guide-for-service/ba-p/4490592</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/core-infrastructure-and-security/implementing-azure-lighthouse-a-technical-guide-for-service/ba-p/4490592</guid><description>Managing resources across multiple tenants is a common challenge for managed service providers (MSPs) and large enterprises. There are many scenarios where you may need to manage resources in many tenants, whether those tenants belong to your organization or they belong to your customers. Without a unified approach, administrators must create accounts in each customer tenant or rely on guest identities, which increases credential sprawl and makes it hard to enforce consistent governance. This also doesn&#8217;t scale, as an administrator who needs to manage many customers would need to separately lo...</description></item><item><title>Public Preview Announcement: Empower Real-Time Security with Microsoft Sentinel&#8217;s CCF Push Feature</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/public-preview-announcement-empower-real-time-security-with/ba-p/4483884</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:36:08 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-sentinel-blog/public-preview-announcement-empower-real-time-security-with/ba-p/4483884</guid><description>In today&#8217;s rapidly evolving threat landscape, organizations need security solutions that deliver actionable insights in real time, not minutes or hours after the fact. Microsoft Sentinel continues to expand its capabilities, driven by a commitment to empower customers and partners with cutting-edge tools for proactive defense. Today, we are excited to announce the public preview of our latest innovation, the Sentinel Codeless Connector Framework (CCF) Push feature. CCF Push addresses a critical need: enabling seamless, automated, and immediate delivery of security data to Sentinel, so teams ca...</description></item><item><title>Introducing Security Dashboard for AI (Now in Public Preview)</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/introducing-security-dashboard-for-ai-now-in-public-preview/ba-p/4494637</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-community/introducing-security-dashboard-for-ai-now-in-public-preview/ba-p/4494637</guid><description>AI proliferation in the enterprise, combined with the emergence of AI governance committees and evolving AI regulations, leaves CISOs and AI risk leaders needing a clear view of their AI risks, such as data leaks, model vulnerabilities, misconfigurations, and unethical agent actions across their entire AI estate, spanning AI platforms, apps, and agents.
53% of security professionals say their current AI risk management needs improvement, presenting an opportunity to better identify, assess and manage risk effectively.1 At the same time, 86% of leaders prefer integrated platforms over fragmente...</description></item><item><title>Navigating the 2026 holiday season:&#160;Insights into Azure&#8217;s DDoS defense</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/navigating-the-2026-holiday-season-insights-into-azure-s-ddos/ba-p/4494932</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:31:33 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/azure-network-security-blog/navigating-the-2026-holiday-season-insights-into-azure-s-ddos/ba-p/4494932</guid><description>The holiday season continues to be one of the most demanding periods for online businesses. Traffic surges, higher transaction volumes, and user expectations for seamless digital experiences all converge, making reliability a non-negotiable requirement. For attackers, this same period presents an opportunity: even brief instability can translate into lost revenue, operational disruption, and reputational impact.&#160;
This year, the most notable shift&#160;wasn&#8217;t&#160;simply the size of attacks, but&#160;how they were executed. We&#160;observed&#160;a rise in&#160;burst style&#160;DDoS events&#8212;fast-ramping,&#160;high-intensity surges dist...</description></item><item><title>Security Review for Microsoft Edge version 145</title><link>https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-baselines/security-review-for-microsoft-edge-version-145/ba-p/4494968</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 11:51:37 GMT</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-security-baselines/security-review-for-microsoft-edge-version-145/ba-p/4494968</guid><description>We have reviewed the new settings in Microsoft Edge version 145 and determined that there are no additional security settings that require enforcement. The Microsoft Edge version 139 security baseline continues to be our recommended configuration which can be downloaded from the Microsoft Security Compliance Toolkit.
&#160;
Microsoft Edge version 145 introduced 11 new Computer and User settings; we have included a spreadsheet listing the new settings to make it easier for you to find.
&#160;
As a friendly reminder, all available settings for Microsoft Edge are documented&#160;here, and all available settings...</description></item></channel>
</rss>
